<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Customer Loyalty &amp;amp; Retention Management Software</title>
    <description>Customer Loyalty &amp;amp; Retention Management Software, integrates with merchant POS systems to give consumers a single identity to earn business-specific rewards</description>
    <link>https://pegke.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://pegke.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2016 09:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2016 09:40:32 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.0.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Anti-spam Legislation India</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-can-spam-act&quot;&gt;The CAN-SPAM Act&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you use email in your business? The CAN-SPAM Act, a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have you stop emailing them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unsolicited Electronic Mail also called “spam” is a growing concern among corporations and individuals. Spamming, once viewed as a mere nuisance, is now posing some alarming problems. In the year 2002 alone, losses to US Corporations due to spamming were a staggering $8.9 billion. In 2003, spam costs to all Non-corporation Internet users were an estimated $255 million . With the increasing number of Internet users in India, the absence of any legislation prohibiting spamming and the dearth of other spam-control measures, it is time the Government took note of this menace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;can-spam-act-india&quot;&gt;CAN-SPAM Act India&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The impact of spam is clearly widespread. Presently, India lacks a specific anti-spam legislation. In consideration of the swelling growth of spam across the globe and the increasing number of Indian users, it is of utmost urgency that a specific legislation is formulated to tackle the issue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;ui highlight&quot;&gt;Presently, India lacks a specific anti-spam legislation.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;in-the-future&quot;&gt;In the future&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the issue being debated across multiple levels, some black and white legislation can be expected in near future. Some quarters have already started calling for an amendment of the IT Act. A TRAI (Telecom Regulatory Authority of India) like regulator, which made regulations like “Do Not Disturb” hotlines for spam SMSs and marketing calls, can also be expected, and any violation can be expected to result in penalty. But in all these, what happens to ConstantContact and other companies providing digital marketing solutions?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-law-says&quot;&gt;The law says&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Don’t use false or misleading header information. Your “From,” “To,” “Reply-To,” and routing information – including the originating domain name and email address – must be accurate and identify the person or business who initiated the message.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Don’t use deceptive subject lines. The subject line must accurately reflect the content of the message.
Identify the message as an ad. The law gives you a lot of leeway in how to do this, but you must disclose clearly and conspicuously that your message is an advertisement.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Tell recipients where you’re located. Your message must include your valid physical postal address. This can be your current street address, a post office box you’ve registered with the U.S. Postal Service, or a private mailbox you’ve registered with a commercial mail receiving agency established under Postal Service regulations.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Tell recipients how to opt out of receiving future email from you. Your message must include a clear and conspicuous explanation of how the recipient can opt out of getting email from you in the future. Craft the notice in a way that’s easy for an ordinary person to recognize, read, and understand. Creative use of type size, color, and location can improve clarity. Give a return email address or another easy Internet-based way to allow people to communicate their choice to you. You may create a menu to allow a recipient to opt out of certain types of messages, but you must include the option to stop all commercial messages from you. Make sure your spam filter doesn’t block these opt-out requests.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Honor opt-out requests promptly. Any opt-out mechanism you offer must be able to process opt-out requests for at least 30 days after you send your message. You must honor a recipient’s opt-out request within 10 business days. You can’t charge a fee, require the recipient to give you any personally identifying information beyond an email address, or make the recipient take any step other than sending a reply email or visiting a single page on an Internet website as a condition for honoring an opt-out request. Once people have told you they don’t want to receive more messages from you, you can’t sell or transfer their email addresses, even in the form of a mailing list. The only exception is that you may transfer the addresses to a company you’ve hired to help you comply with the CAN-SPAM Act.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Monitor what others are doing on your behalf. The law makes clear that even if you hire another company to handle your email marketing, you can’t contract away your legal responsibility to comply with the law. Both the company whose product is promoted in the message and the company that actually sends the message may be held legally responsible.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;ui header medium source&quot;&gt;Sources&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/CAN-SPAM_Act_of_2003&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;http://www.legalservicesindia.com/articles/spamli.htm&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;http://cis-india.org/internet-governance/blog/anti-spam-laws-in-different-jurisdictions&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;http://yourstory.com/2015/01/company-use-spam-emails-marketing-watch/&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>https://pegke.com/blog/can-spam-act-india</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pegke.com/blog/can-spam-act-india</guid>
        
        <category>terms</category>
        
        
        <category>blogs</category>
        
        <category>CAN-SPAM</category>
        
        <category>Email</category>
        
        <category>Terms</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Pegke interacts with your POS/inventory</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-is-pegke-customer-loyalty-program&quot;&gt;What is Pegke Customer Loyalty Program&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pegke is an easy to use customer loyalty program or a reward point system, beneficial to both the business and the customer. Businesses drive attention of customers through customer loyalty programs by offering fantastic ways to reward and say thank you to their customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;ui highlight&quot;&gt;The point of sale (POS) is the time and place where a retail transaction is completed. It is the point at which a customer makes a payment to the merchant in exchange for goods or after provision of a service.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;how-pegke-customer-loyalty-program-integrates-with-your-pos&quot;&gt;How Pegke Customer Loyalty Program integrates with your POS&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At Pegke, we have multiple ways of integrating your POS with Pegke cloud platform. Which includes and not limited to API, Coupon Scan and Tablet. Lets take a look at each of them in detail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;ui image fluid lazy&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/pegke-api-workflow.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;pegke api&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Manual Interaction
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pegke Web Dashboard:&lt;/strong&gt;
In Pegke web dashboard you will be having a simple form to enter your customers details, transactions and the points you want to give them. This is useful when you don’t have a huge number of transactions happening in a single day.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pegke Tablet Application:&lt;/strong&gt;
As a Pegke Business you will have a Android tablet application where your customers can check-in, browse your products and offers and even to redeem an item from your business. As an extra feature we have added some basic insights of your businesses performance in the Tablet app.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Automated Interaction
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pegke HTTP API:&lt;/strong&gt;
Each business will have access to Pegke Cloud HTTP API to interact with the platform. Business can integrate Pegke Cloud HTTP API with their own platform or web application to talk to Pegke Cloud HTTP API. We will be having strict restriction policies and security mechanism to identify and prevent fraud.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;POS/PG Interaction:&lt;/strong&gt;
Pegke support team will help you or your IT team to integrate the system to Pegke. We already have serious integrations for multiple types of POS/PG. Talk to us first before you try something out.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Coupon Scan:&lt;/strong&gt;
One of the super fast method to integrate Pegke with your business if you’re in Fast-moving consumer goods (FMCG).&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;redeemable-items&quot;&gt;Redeemable Items&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each business can define their own redeemable items through pegke web dashboard, business will have option to specify the points required to redeem an item or any specific notes to it. All these items will be published on the Business page of Pegke website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;how-to-redeem-pegke-points&quot;&gt;How to redeem Pegke Points.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a consumer, they always have the Pegke mobile app to check, manage their Pegke Accounts. User can visit available products on each Pegke Business and the points they on each business and redeem right away from the mobile app.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Upon a successful redeem, corresponding business will be notified and will have a list of redeemed items and users on the web dashboard.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>https://pegke.com/blog/how-pegke-customer-loyalty-program-interacts-your-posinventory</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pegke.com/blog/how-pegke-customer-loyalty-program-interacts-your-posinventory</guid>
        
        <category>Loyalty Program</category>
        
        
        <category>blogs</category>
        
        <category>Loyalty Program</category>
        
        <category>Pegke Loyalty Software</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Top 5 Customer Loyalty Trends of 2016</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;In all actuality client experience does make a difference. Brands that can give fun, satisfying encounters through great deals stages and additional items like dedication projects have the capacity to catch more rehash clients, who pivot and get new clients they could call their own through image evangelism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Omni-channel Engagement&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Enthusiastic LOYALTY&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Client examination takes focal point of the audience.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Personalization and accomplice showcasing&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Experiential prizes = greatest effect.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;ui image fluid lazy&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/top-5-customer-loyalty-trends-of-2016.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Customer Loyalty Trends Of 2016&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;omni-channel-engagement&quot;&gt;1. Omni-channel Engagement&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Customer Loyalty Program venturing past the normal deals limits is one sign that marking has turn out to be more about thoughts than items. Clients have day in and day out access to the brands they cherish through online networking and cell phones. Brands, thusly, have new venues to achieve their center business without needing to envision pedestrian activity or exposures to outbound showcasing promotions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Drawing in clients through substance or balanced cooperations makes a relationship that does not end at the checkout line. Brands that have the capacity to outfit the force of these numerous levels of correspondence to convey a firm, including brand message will be more inclined to succeed in an inexorably advanced environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;enthusiastic-loyalty&quot;&gt;2. Enthusiastic LOYALTY&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reliability projects are customarily considered as a rationale based quality suggestion. “Take an interest through these buys and get more esteem consequently,” are the directions conveyed to clients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nonetheless, this simply right-cerebrum driven support is now and again insufficient. Client dedication can be all the more adequately earned through enthusiastic, left-cerebrum thinking also.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;client-examination-takes-focal-point-of-the-audience&quot;&gt;3. Client examination takes focal point of the audience.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Measuring dedication has never been simple. For quite a long time, we’ve moved around various imperative KPIs. Details like LTV, RFM, recency of visit, number of prizes recovered, number of individuals in your reliability system, and others have helped us gage regardless of whether our endeavors in un-averingness are working.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;personalization-and-accomplice-showcasing&quot;&gt;4. Personalization and accomplice showcasing&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are bullish on this one. BigDoor is really fixated on partner showcasing, as we trust its vital to truly knowing how well your un-averingness endeavors are performing. Indeed, we keep a control client gather in every customer execution of our dedication program for this accurate reason — to demonstrate the amount of quality our innovation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;experiential-prizes--greatest-effect&quot;&gt;5. Experiential prizes = greatest effect.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Prizes matter. We all know this. The previous couple of years we’ve seen the greatest brands on the planet re-put into their clients and genuinely welcome them in an assortment of ways. We think 2015 will get a shift how clients are remunerated for dedication. As opposed to just give out rebates or your most recent organization swag, we think brands will conceptualize energizing, novel, experiential prizes for their most connected with clients.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>https://pegke.com/blog/top-5-customer-loyalty-trends-2016</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pegke.com/blog/top-5-customer-loyalty-trends-2016</guid>
        
        <category>trends</category>
        
        
        <category>blogs</category>
        
        <category>Loyalty Program</category>
        
        <category>Loyalty Trends</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Loyalty over the Holidays</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Amid the extreme center of attention on scoring revenue in a sea of competitors, it can be easy to omit what must be the precedence — successful a patron who sticks round long after the ultimate slice of ham is eaten and the lights come down. If the value of loyalty escapes you, understand this: consistent with Harvard business review, growing patron retention rates by just 5% raises gains with the aid of 25% to 95%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;build-personal-connections-with-data&quot;&gt;1. Build personal connections with data&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a be taught released in the Journal of applied Social Psychology, researchers learned that waiters were competent to broaden their suggestions by 23% quite simply by offering their purchasers a 2nd set of mints and framing the act as if it had been for them and them best.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The lesson to study right here is that a private, significant connection is predominant to getting probably the most out of persons, and how to attain that is through purchaser information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even some thing as simple as collecting data on whether or not a bought item is a gift can be utilized to ship a pleasant follow-up that offers the buyer something particular for himself or herself at the side of a question about how the present was once obtained.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;make-the-small-print-a-big-deal&quot;&gt;2. Make the small print a big deal&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That is notably actual for the ever-trendy reward voucher buy, where traditionally phrases and conditions are murkier territory. Being entirely obvious can ruin down what in any other case perhaps a barrier to buy and ensure the buyer and recipient’s experiences are incredibly confident.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;bring-real-life-online-and-vice-versa&quot;&gt;3. Bring real life, online and vice versa&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are still occupied with your small business internet site, social media platforms, web publication and actual lifestyles presence as separate entities with separate strategies: discontinue. The satisfactory advertising systems reside throughout your brand’s whole presence, creating one cohesive message that shows the world what you stand for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Starbucks does this totally good with each and every celebration. This 12 months’s weird pink cup controversy is a testimony to how iconic the seasonal design tweak really is, and the company seamlessly integrates this in-retailer activation on-line with an Instagram pink Cup Contest which furnished content for Pinterest, facebook, and Twitter and a design tweak to deliver the festivities to the industry website. Regardless of a undoubtedly-large marketing price range, Starbucks still heralds easy recommendations and consistency throughout platforms - and strikes success every time.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>https://pegke.com/blog/customer-loyalty-over-holidays</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pegke.com/blog/customer-loyalty-over-holidays</guid>
        
        
        <category>blogs</category>
        
        <category>Holidays</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Customer Retention Strategies</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The results of customer retention additionally compound after some time, and in at times unforeseen ways. Indeed, even a modest change in customer retention can course through a business framework and increase after some time. The subsequent impact on long haul benefit and development shouldn’t be thought little of.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pegke can acquaint you with various basic customer retention techniques that will cost you or nothing to actualize. Behind every system recorded here there is a top to bottom regulated procedure that will build your customer retention altogether once actualized, and will have an enormous effect on your business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;ui image fluid lazy&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://pegke.com/sites/default/files/uploads/customer_retention.png&quot; alt=&quot;Customer Retention Strategies&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;reducing-attrition&quot;&gt;1. Reducing Attrition&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For all intents and purposes each business loses a few customers, however few ever measure or perceive what number of their customers get to be inert. Most organizations, incidentally, contribute a tremendous measure of time, exertion and cost constructing that introductory customer relationship. At that point they let that relationship go unattended, sometimes notwithstanding losing enthusiasm when the deal been made, or far more detestable, they desert the customer when an effortlessly cured issue happens, just to need to spend another little fortune to supplant that customer. The least demanding approach to develop your business is not to lose your customers. When you stop the spillage, it’s frequently conceivable to twofold or triple your development rate in light of the fact that you’re no more compelled to make up lost ground just to stop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;bring-back-the-lost-sheep&quot;&gt;2. Bring back the “lost sheep”&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s little point in committing gigantic assets to creating new customers when 25-60% of your torpid customers will be responsive to your endeavors to recover their business on the off chance that you approach them the right route, with the right offer. Reactivating customers who definitely know you and your item is one of the least demanding, fastest approaches to expand your incomes. Re-reaching and helping them to remember your presence, discovering why they’re no more purchasing, defeating their complaints and showing that despite everything you esteem and appreciation them will more often than not bring about a gigantic abundance of offers and radically expanded incomes in a matter of days … and will prompt some of your best and most steadfast customer&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-complaint-is-a-gift&quot;&gt;3. A complaint is a gift&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;96 percent of disappointed customers don’t whine. They simply leave, and you’ll never know why. That is on the grounds that they regularly don’t know how to grumble, or can’t be annoyed, or are excessively panicked, or don’t accept it’ll have any effect. Whilst they may not let you know what’s wrong, they will surely tell a lot of others. A framework for uncovering protests can in this way be the soul of your business, in light of the fact that customers who gripe are giving you a blessing, regardless they’re conversing with you, they’re giving you another chance to return them to a condition of fulfillment and enjoyment them and the way in which you react gives you another opportunity to demonstrate what you’re made of and make significantly more noteworthy customer dedication.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;frequent-communications-calendar&quot;&gt;4. Frequent Communications Calendar&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Abstain from losing your customers by building connections and staying in contact utilizing a moving schedule of interchanges. This is a modified succession of letters, occasions, telephone calls, “thank you’s”, uncommon offers, subsequent meet-ups, enchantment minutes, and cards or notes with an individual touch and so on that happen continually and consequently at characterized focuses in the pre-deals, deals and post-deals process. Individuals not just react to this emphatically, they truly value it in light of the fact that they feel esteemed and vital. It recognizes them, keeps them educated, counterbalances post-buy questions, strengthens the reason they’re working with you and makes them feel a piece of your business so they need to return over and over.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>https://pegke.com/blog/customer-retention-strategies</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pegke.com/blog/customer-retention-strategies</guid>
        
        <category>Retention</category>
        
        
        <category>blogs</category>
        
        <category>Loyalty Program</category>
        
        <category>Retention</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Check your points</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;ui grid stackable&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;column eight wide&quot;&gt;
    Download our app from app store and earn poits from the installing itself,
    keep the app ready for your next purchase.

    &lt;div class=&quot;ui divider hidden&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;div class=&quot;ohidden&quot;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;ui divider horizontal&quot;&gt;
        Not a Member Yet?
      &lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;div class=&quot;ui green button animated big fluid&quot; tabindex=&quot;0&quot;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;visible content&quot;&gt;Get the Mobile App&lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;hidden content&quot;&gt;earn loyalty points &lt;i class=&quot;heart icon red&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;div class=&quot;ui divider horizontal&quot;&gt;
      Chose your platform
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;a href=&quot;https://pegke.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;green android huge icon&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;a href=&quot;https://pegke.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;blue windows huge icon&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;a href=&quot;https://pegke.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;black apple huge icon&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;

  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;column six wide&quot;&gt;

    &lt;form class=&quot;ui form&quot; id=&quot;checkpoints&quot; method=&quot;post&quot; action=&quot;#&quot;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;ui form&quot;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;field ui big fluid input&quot;&gt;
          &lt;input type=&quot;tel&quot; name=&quot;phone&quot; placeholder=&quot;Phone Number&quot;&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;field ui fluid&quot;&gt;
          &lt;div class=&quot;ui search big selection dropdown&quot;&gt;
            &lt;input type=&quot;hidden&quot; name=&quot;country&quot;&gt;
            &lt;i class=&quot;dropdown icon&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
            &lt;div class=&quot;default text&quot;&gt;Select Country&lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;div class=&quot;menu&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;ar&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;ar flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;Argentina&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;au&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;au flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;Australia&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;bh&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;bh flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;Bahrain&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;be&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;be flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;Belgium&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;br&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;br flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;Brazil&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;vg&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;vg flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;British Virgin Islands&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;cm&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;cm flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;Cameroon&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;ca&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;ca flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;Canada&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;cz&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;cz flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;Czech Republic&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;dk&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;dk flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;Denmark&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;dm&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;dm flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;Dominica&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;eg&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;eg flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;Egypt&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;gb&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;gb flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;England&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;eu&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;eu flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;European Union&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;fr&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;fr flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;France&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;de&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;de flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;Germany&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;gr&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;gr flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;Greece&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;gl&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;gl flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;Greenland&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;hu&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;hu flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;Hungary&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;is&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;is flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;Iceland&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;in&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;in flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;India&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;ie&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;ie flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;Ireland&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;it&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;it flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;Italy&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;kw&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;kw flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;Kuwait&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;lu&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;lu flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;Luxembourg&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;my&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;my flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;Malaysia&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;mx&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;mx flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;Mexico&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;nl&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;nl flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;Netherlands&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;nz&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;nz flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;New Zealand&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;no&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;no flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;Norway&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;om&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;om flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;Oman&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;pl&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;pl flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;Poland&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;pt&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;pt flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;Portugal&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;qa&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;qa flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;Qatar&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;sa&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;sa flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;Saudi Arabia&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;sg&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;sg flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;Singapore&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;es&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;es flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;Spain&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;lk&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;lk flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;Sri Lanka&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;se&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;se flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;Sweden&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;ch&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;ch flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;Switzerland&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;tw&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;tw flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;Taiwan&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;th&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;th flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;Thailand&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;ae&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;ae flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;United Arab Emirates&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;us&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;us flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;United States&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;um&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;um flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;Us Minor Islands&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;vi&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;vi flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;Us Virgin Islands&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;item&quot; data-value=&quot;vn&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;vn flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;Vietnam&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

          &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;button id=&quot;sbmit&quot; class=&quot;ui button big blue&quot; type=&quot;submit&quot;&gt;Submit&lt;/button&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;ui error message&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/form&gt;

  &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>https://pegke.com/check-points/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pegke.com/check-points/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Customer Loyalty Program Software for Restaurants</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Pegke is a customer loyalty programs for restaurants - as well, which utilizes the Smartphone and Tablet to manage the program; Pegke is the one solution that allows restaurants to create loyalty campaigns enabling them to attract more customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Customer loyalty has been vital to restaurants of numerous types subsequent to the idea of an “restaurant” was made. Loyal customers are the ones who will return regularly and spend as often as possible, which helps restaurants of all sizes meet their main concerns. However building loyalty is not another idea for eatery proprietors, the strategies used to approach building customer loyalty have changed throughout the years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;ui image fluid&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://pegke.com/sites/default/files/uploads/customer-loyalty-program-software-for-restaurants.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Customer Loyalty Program Software for Restaurants&quot; title=&quot;Customer Loyalty Program Software for Restaurants&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;traditionally-customer-loyalty-has-been-managed-by-one-of-the-following-methods&quot;&gt;Traditionally Customer loyalty has been managed by one of the following methods.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;punch-cards&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Punch cards&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Punch cards are one among the earliest kinds of loyalty building techniques. although the inducement of “buy 10 meals and obtain the 11th free” still appeals to some diners, it solely permits restaurant owners to reward customers for one action out of the many that they take.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;general-on-bill-discounts&quot;&gt;General on-bill discounts&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Offering a discount to all customers might seem like a generous move by the restaurant, but is it really helping your brand build lasting loyalty? Unfortunately, research shows otherwise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The fact of the matter is that frequent customers already like your restaurant, and although a couple bucks off on a menu item is always nice, it’s not why they keep coming back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;is-this-for-the-future&quot;&gt;Is this for the future?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Of course its not&lt;/strong&gt;, thats why we made a &lt;strong&gt;Customer Loyalty &amp;amp; Retention Management Platform&lt;/strong&gt; which utilizes the Smartphone and Tablet to manage the program; Pegke is the one solution that allows restaurants to create loyalty campaigns enabling them to attract more customer flow to the restaurant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;advantages-of-using-pegke-customer-loyalty-program-for-a-restaurant&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Advantages of using Pegke Customer Loyalty Program for a Restaurant&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;specialized-store-front&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specialized store front&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A very robust and customizable store front for your online store. You can make this place to promote your latest offers and Nuggets you publish via the vendor dashboard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;store-settings&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Store Settings&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can customize the check-in interval for your customers on your shop. Its a few clicks away. Also you can switch from price range store or check-in store anytime based on your Subscription level&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;demographics&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Demographics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is one of the best part of Pegke, you can view detailed graphs of your stores performance in real time, which will help you restructure your offers and Nuggets , if necessary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;send-push-messages&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Send Push Messages&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Send Push messages to the customers. One of the impressive ways to enlighten customers, pickup sales and customer satisfaction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thats not all, read the complete list of Pegke &lt;a href=&quot;https://pegke.com/vendor-app-features&quot;&gt;Customer Loyalty Program Features&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>https://pegke.com/blog/customer-loyalty-program-software-for-restaurants</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pegke.com/blog/customer-loyalty-program-software-for-restaurants</guid>
        
        <category>Loyalty</category>
        
        <category>Restaurants</category>
        
        
        <category>blogs</category>
        
        <category>Loyalty Program</category>
        
        <category>Restaurants</category>
        
        <category>Loyalty Software</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Technology stack</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;ui aligned segment stack pegke&quot;&gt;

  &lt;div class=&quot;ui divider horizontal&quot;&gt;Application and Data&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;ui tiny images&quot;&gt;
    
    &lt;img data-src=&quot;/public/img/stack/nginx.png&quot; data-content=&quot; Nxinx&quot; class=&quot;ui image rounded tstack&quot; /&gt;
    
    &lt;img data-src=&quot;/public/img/stack/nodejs.png&quot; data-content=&quot; NodeJs&quot; class=&quot;ui image rounded tstack&quot; /&gt;
    
    &lt;img data-src=&quot;/public/img/stack/php.jpg&quot; data-content=&quot; PHP 7&quot; class=&quot;ui image rounded tstack&quot; /&gt;
    
    &lt;img data-src=&quot;/public/img/stack/ruby.png&quot; data-content=&quot; Ruby&quot; class=&quot;ui image rounded tstack&quot; /&gt;
    
    &lt;img data-src=&quot;/public/img/stack/drupal8.png&quot; data-content=&quot; Drupal 8&quot; class=&quot;ui image rounded tstack&quot; /&gt;
    
    &lt;img data-src=&quot;/public/img/stack/oauth-2.jpg&quot; data-content=&quot; OAuth 2.0&quot; class=&quot;ui image rounded tstack&quot; /&gt;
    
    &lt;img data-src=&quot;/public/img/stack/markdown.png&quot; data-content=&quot; Markdown&quot; class=&quot;ui image rounded tstack&quot; /&gt;
    
    &lt;img data-src=&quot;/public/img/stack/javascript.jpg&quot; data-content=&quot; Javascript&quot; class=&quot;ui image rounded tstack&quot; /&gt;
    
    &lt;img data-src=&quot;/public/img/stack/mysql.png&quot; data-content=&quot; MySQL&quot; class=&quot;ui image rounded tstack&quot; /&gt;
    
    &lt;img data-src=&quot;/public/img/stack/mongodb.png&quot; data-content=&quot; MongoDB&quot; class=&quot;ui image rounded tstack&quot; /&gt;
    
    &lt;img data-src=&quot;/public/img/stack/memcached.png&quot; data-content=&quot; Memcached&quot; class=&quot;ui image rounded tstack&quot; /&gt;
    
    &lt;img data-src=&quot;/public/img/stack/backbone.png&quot; data-content=&quot; Backbone.js&quot; class=&quot;ui image rounded tstack&quot; /&gt;
    
    &lt;img data-src=&quot;/public/img/stack/HTML5.png&quot; data-content=&quot; HTML 5&quot; class=&quot;ui image rounded tstack&quot; /&gt;
    
    &lt;img data-src=&quot;/public/img/stack/semantic.png&quot; data-content=&quot; Semantic UI&quot; class=&quot;ui image rounded tstack&quot; /&gt;
    
    &lt;img data-src=&quot;/public/img/stack/bootstrap.jpg&quot; data-content=&quot; Twitter Bootstrap&quot; class=&quot;ui image rounded tstack&quot; /&gt;
    
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;div class=&quot;ui divider horizontal&quot;&gt;Utilities&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;ui tiny images&quot;&gt;
    
    &lt;img data-src=&quot;/public/img/stack/gh-pages.png&quot; data-content=&quot; Github Pages&quot; class=&quot;ui image rounded tstack&quot; /&gt;
    
    &lt;img data-src=&quot;/public/img/stack/analytics.png&quot; data-content=&quot; Google Analytics&quot; class=&quot;ui image rounded tstack&quot; /&gt;
    
    &lt;img data-src=&quot;/public/img/stack/git.png&quot; data-content=&quot; Git&quot; class=&quot;ui image rounded tstack&quot; /&gt;
    
    &lt;img data-src=&quot;/public/img/stack/mandrill.png&quot; data-content=&quot; Transactional Emails&quot; class=&quot;ui image rounded tstack&quot; /&gt;
    
    &lt;img data-src=&quot;/public/img/stack/mixpanel.png&quot; data-content=&quot; Mixpanel Analytics&quot; class=&quot;ui image rounded tstack&quot; /&gt;
    
    &lt;img data-src=&quot;/public/img/stack/cloudflare.png&quot; data-content=&quot; CDN&quot; class=&quot;ui image rounded tstack&quot; /&gt;
    
    &lt;img data-src=&quot;/public/img/stack/digitalocean.png&quot; data-content=&quot; Digital Ocean&quot; class=&quot;ui image rounded tstack&quot; /&gt;
    
    &lt;img data-src=&quot;/public/img/stack/jekyll.png&quot; data-content=&quot; Jekyll Static Site Generator&quot; class=&quot;ui image rounded tstack&quot; /&gt;
    
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;div class=&quot;ui divider horizontal&quot;&gt;DevOps&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;ui tiny images&quot;&gt;
    
    &lt;img data-src=&quot;/public/img/stack/jenkins.png&quot; data-content=&quot; Jenkins CI&quot; class=&quot;ui image rounded tstack&quot; /&gt;
    
    &lt;img data-src=&quot;/public/img/stack/github.png&quot; data-content=&quot; GitHub Social Coding&quot; class=&quot;ui image rounded tstack&quot; /&gt;
    
    &lt;img data-src=&quot;/public/img/stack/bitbucket.png&quot; data-content=&quot; Bitbucket - private repositories&quot; class=&quot;ui image rounded tstack&quot; /&gt;
    
    &lt;img data-src=&quot;/public/img/stack/new-relic.jpg&quot; data-content=&quot; New Relic&quot; class=&quot;ui image rounded tstack&quot; /&gt;
    
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;div class=&quot;ui divider horizontal&quot;&gt;Business Tools&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;ui tiny images&quot;&gt;
    
    &lt;img data-src=&quot;/public/img/stack/slack.png&quot; data-content=&quot; Slack&quot; class=&quot;ui image rounded tstack&quot; /&gt;
    
    &lt;img data-src=&quot;/public/img/stack/trello.png&quot; data-content=&quot; Trello&quot; class=&quot;ui image rounded tstack&quot; /&gt;
    
    &lt;img data-src=&quot;/public/img/stack/apps-for-work.png&quot; data-content=&quot; Google Apps for work&quot; class=&quot;ui image rounded tstack&quot; /&gt;
    
  &lt;/div&gt;


&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;ui divider hidden&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;ui text green segment pegke&quot;&gt;
  &lt;h3 class=&quot;ui header&quot;&gt;We Love Developers&lt;/h3&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    You&#39;ve came this far, we appreciate that... :)
  &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;div class=&quot;ui divider horizontal&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;ui huge heart rating&quot; data-rating=&quot;1&quot; data-max-rating=&quot;1&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;h4&gt;Quick Links&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;ui bulleted list&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a class=&quot;item&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://github.com/pegkeloyalty&quot;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;a class=&quot;item&quot; href=&quot;/about/brand-guidelines&quot;&gt;Brand Guidelines&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;a class=&quot;item&quot; href=&quot;/about/technology-stack&quot;&gt;Technology stack&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;a class=&quot;item&quot; href=&quot;/contact&quot;&gt;Support&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;a class=&quot;item&quot; href=&quot;/about/careers&quot;&gt;Join Our Team&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;a class=&quot;item&quot; href=&quot;/api/&quot;&gt;API&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;/api/faq&quot; class=&quot;item&quot;&gt;Developer FAQ&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;ui divider hidden&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>https://pegke.com/about/technology-stack</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pegke.com/about/technology-stack</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Brand Guidelines</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;ui two column stackable grid&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;column&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h2&gt;Usage&lt;/h2&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        The Pegke Loyalty marks include the Pegke Loyalty name and logo, and any word, phrase, image, or other designation that identifies the source or origin of any of Pegke Loyalty&#39;s products. Please don&#39;t modify the marks or use them in a confusing way, including suggesting sponsorship or endorsement by Pegke Loyalty, or in a way that confuses Pegke Loyalty with another brand (including your own).
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;column&quot;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;ui small images&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;http://placehold.it/350&quot; class=&quot;ui image rounded fluid&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;http://placehold.it/350&quot; class=&quot;ui image rounded fluid&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;http://placehold.it/350&quot; class=&quot;ui image rounded fluid&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;ui divider hidden&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;ui divider hidden&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;ui container center aligned&quot;&gt;
    &lt;h3&gt;Download Logos&lt;/h3&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;
      Our brand assets can be downloaded from Brandfolder.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;div class=&quot;ui labeled button&quot; tabindex=&quot;0&quot;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;ui red button&quot;&gt;
        &lt;i class=&quot;download icon&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; Download
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;a class=&quot;ui basic red left pointing label&quot; href=&quot;#download&quot;&gt;
        1,048
      &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;


  &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3 class=&quot;ui header teal&quot;&gt;Visual design of your website or application&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Design your site with unique branding and logos. Do not copy or imitate the look and feel of the Pegke Loyalty website or apps, as this could create user confusion.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;If utilizing the Pegke Loyalty API to support your service or application, you must feature a prominent banner noting your service is &quot;not created by, affiliated with, or supported by Pegke Loyalty, Inc.&quot;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;You must not use, display, mirror or frame (including in meta-tags or hidden text) Pegke Loyalty websites, or any individual element of Pegke Loyalty websites, Pegke Loyalty&#39;s name, trademarks, logos or other proprietary information, or the layout and design of any page or form contained on a page.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;ui divider horizontal&quot;&gt;🎶&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Naming&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;You&#39;re entitled to say that your website or application is integrated with Pegke Loyalty (we like people integrating with Pegke Loyalty!), but please don&#39;t use the Pegke Loyalty marks as part of the name of your company, application, product, or service, or in any logo you create.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Do not register a domain containing “Pegke Loyalty”, misspellings, transliterations or similar variations thereof. That would be very uncool.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Do not apply for a trademark with a name including “Pegke Loyalty”, the Pegke Loyalty hash, transliterations or similar variations thereof.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;ui divider horizontal&quot;&gt;🌐&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;General Info&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    By using the Pegke Loyalty marks you agree to follow these guidelines as well as our Terms of Service and all our rules and policies. Pegke Loyalty reserves the right to cancel, modify, or change the permission in these guidelines at any time at its sole discretion. For further information about use of the Pegke Loyalty name and trademarks, please contact &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:feedback@pegke.com&quot;&gt;feedback@pegke.com&lt;/a&gt;.
  &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>https://pegke.com/about/brand-guidelines</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pegke.com/about/brand-guidelines</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pegke Status</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;ui grid stackable&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;column ten wide&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;ui icon success big message&quot;&gt;
      &lt;i class=&quot;checkmark box icon large monitor only&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;content&quot;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;header&quot;&gt;All Systems Operational #PegkeStat&lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Last updated on: &lt;span id=&quot;lstmod&quot;&gt;---&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;ui divider hidden&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div id=&quot;pegkestat&quot; class=&quot;ui loading segment basic&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;ui divider hidden&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;ui divider hidden&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;h4&gt;Past Incidents&lt;/h4&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;
      To know about past incidents please subscribe to &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hashtag/PegkeStat&quot;&gt;#PegkeStat&lt;/a&gt; on Twitter
    &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;column six wide&quot;&gt;
    &lt;a class=&quot;twitter-timeline&quot; data-dnt=&quot;true&quot; href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hashtag/PegkeStat&quot; data-widget-id=&quot;682961542715813888&quot;&gt;#PegkeStat Tweets&lt;/a&gt; &lt;script&gt;!function(d,s,id){var js,fjs=d.getElementsByTagName(s)[0],p=/^http:/.test(d.location)?&#39;http&#39;:&#39;https&#39;;if(!d.getElementById(id)){js=d.createElement(s);js.id=id;js.src=p+&quot;://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot;;fjs.parentNode.insertBefore(js,fjs);}}(document,&quot;script&quot;,&quot;twitter-wjs&quot;);&lt;/script&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>https://pegke.com/about/system-status</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pegke.com/about/system-status</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Join Our Team</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;ui grid stackable&quot;&gt;

    &lt;div class=&quot;column ten wide&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        A lot of companies talk about culture--their awesome office, fun events and great perks. But we view culture differently. We believe it&#39;s about rallying people who enjoy each other&#39;s company and respect each other&#39;s skill. It&#39;s about working alongside people you rely on to spar with you intellectually one moment, then grab tacos with you the next.
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        We&#39;ve created a culture that rewards bright, driven, and fun-loving people. We take our work seriously. But ourselves? Not so much.
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;strong&gt;At Pegke Rewards &amp;#8482; you can...&lt;/strong&gt;
      &lt;ul class=&quot;ui list&quot;&gt;
        &lt;li class=&quot;item&quot;&gt;Power Customer Success&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li class=&quot;item&quot;&gt;Solve Meaningful Problems&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li class=&quot;item&quot;&gt;Build and Promote Great Technology&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li class=&quot;item&quot;&gt;Work with Brilliant People&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li class=&quot;item&quot;&gt;Work in the interesting new technologies&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li class=&quot;item&quot;&gt;Explore the &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Blockchain&quot;&gt;Blockchain&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;/ul&gt;
      Say hello to: &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:hello@pegke.com&quot;&gt;hello@pegke.com&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;ui hidden divider&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;ui hidden divider&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/pegkeapp&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;twitter icon large grey&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://plus.google.com/+Pegke&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;google plus icon large grey&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://fb.com/pegkeapp&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;facebook icon large grey&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://pegke.com/feed.xml&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;rss icon large grey&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;

    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;div class=&quot;column six wide&quot;&gt;
      &lt;img data-src=&quot;/public/img/careers.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Pegke Team&quot; class=&quot;ui image lazy fluid rounded&quot; /&gt;
      &lt;h5 class=&quot;ui divider horizontal&quot;&gt;Contact Us&lt;/h5&gt;
      &lt;div itemscope=&quot;&quot; itemtype=&quot;http://schema.org/Organization&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a itemprop=&quot;url&quot; href=&quot;https://pegke.com&quot;&gt;&lt;div itemprop=&quot;name&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pegke Rewards &amp;#8482;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https://pegke.com/assets/customer-loyalty-program.png&quot; itemprop=&quot;image&quot; class=&quot;ohidden&quot; alt=&quot;Pegke Loyalty&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;div itemprop=&quot;address&quot; itemscope=&quot;&quot; itemtype=&quot;http://schema.org/PostalAddress&quot;&gt;
    &lt;span itemprop=&quot;streetAddress&quot;&gt;G3B, Thejaswini&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
    &lt;span itemprop=&quot;postOfficeBoxNumber&quot;&gt;Technopark Campus&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
    &lt;span itemprop=&quot;addressLocality&quot;&gt;Trivandrum&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
    &lt;span itemprop=&quot;addressRegion&quot;&gt;Kerala&lt;/span&gt; -
    &lt;span itemprop=&quot;postalCode&quot;&gt;695581&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
    &lt;span itemprop=&quot;addressCountry&quot;&gt;India&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
    &lt;a itemprop=&quot;email&quot; href=&quot;mailto:hello@pegke.com&quot;&gt;hello@pegke.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
    &lt;i class=&quot;in flag&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;a itemprop=&quot;telephone&quot; href=&quot;tel:+914714000056&quot;&gt;+91 (471) 400-0056&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;br /&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>https://pegke.com/about/careers</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pegke.com/about/careers</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Developer Docs</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;ui stackable grid&quot;&gt;

  &lt;div class=&quot;twelve wide column&quot;&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Allows a registered merchants to obtain an OAuth 2 Bearer Token, which can be used to make API requests without a user context. This is called Application-only authentication.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;A Bearer Token may be invalidated using oauth2/invalidate_token. Once a Bearer Token has been invalidated, new creation attempts will yield a different Bearer Token and usage of the previous token will no longer be allowed.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Only one bearer token may exist outstanding for an application, and repeated requests to this method will yield the same already-existent token until it has been invalidated.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;As with all API v1.1 methods, HTTPS is always required.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Successful responses include a JSON-structure describing the awarded Bearer Token.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Tokens received by this method should be cached. If attempted too frequently, requests will be rejected with a HTTP 403 with code 99.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;div id=&quot;context&quot; class=&quot;ui text&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h2&gt;Getting started with pegke API&lt;/h2&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;ui grid stackable hashnav&quot;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;six wide column&quot;&gt;

          &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#web&quot;&gt;Web API&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;
An HTTP/JSON based API that allows you to build applications that interact with Pegke in more complex ways.
&lt;/p&gt;

          &lt;ul class=&quot;ui list&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#auth&quot;&gt;Authenticate&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#give&quot;&gt;Give Loyalty Points&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#search&quot;&gt;Search User&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#validate&quot;&gt;Validate a Redeem&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#shistory&quot;&gt;Store History&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#uhistory&quot;&gt;User History&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;six wide column ui&quot;&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#rta&quot;&gt;Realtime Activity API&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;
A WebSocket-based API that allows you to stream your in-store activity.
&lt;/p&gt;

          &lt;ul class=&quot;ui list&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#store&quot;&gt;Store Activity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;ui divider horizontal header blue&quot;&gt;
        &lt;h2 id=&quot;web&quot;&gt;Web API&lt;/h2&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;div class=&quot;ui divider hidden&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://apigility.org/documentation/auth/authentication-oauth2&quot;&gt;OAuth 2&lt;/a&gt; is a protocol that lets your app request authorization to private details in a customer’s and Business data to your application.&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
You’ll need to collect your OAuth tokens to make API calls, each merchant account is assigned a unique Client ID and Client Secret which will be used in the OAuth flow. The Client Secret should not be shared.
&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc6750&quot;&gt;Bearer Tokens&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
The most common OAuth 2 token type. It provides very little in terms of security and relies heavily upon the ability of the client to keep the token secret &lt;a href=&quot;http://oauthlib.readthedocs.org/en/latest/oauth2/tokens/bearer.html&quot;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;h3 id=&quot;auth&quot;&gt;Authenticate&lt;/h3&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;Since we are using &lt;strong&gt;OAuth 2.0 Bearer Token&lt;/strong&gt; you are always authorized &lt;strong&gt;if and only if&lt;/strong&gt; you are passing the header&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-http&quot;&gt;Authorization: Bearer YOUR-ACCES-TOKEN
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

      &lt;h3 id=&quot;give&quot;&gt;Give Loyalty Points&lt;/h3&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;You can give Loyalty points to any customer using &lt;strong&gt;Customer ID, Mobile Number, or Email&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-http&quot;&gt;POST /entity/user?_format=json HTTP/1.1
Host: dashboard.pegke.com/v1
Content-Type: application/json
Authorization: Bearer RvnIMUDspJs_RFFIKqWYF4zGMDJL9C4OrXHao3-mrZ8

{
  &quot;idType&quot;: &quot;mob&quot; // either mob, cid, email
  &quot;mob&quot;: 9826471001 // 10 Digit Phone number. must match with the value of &lt;strong&gt;idType&lt;/strong&gt;
  &quot;points&quot;: 10 // the points
}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

      &lt;h4 id=&quot;response&quot;&gt;Response&lt;/h4&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Success&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;pre class=&quot;success&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-http&quot;&gt;HTTP/1.1 200 OK
Content-Type: application/json

{
    &quot;access_token&quot;: &quot;907c762e069589c2cd2a229cdae7b8778caa9f07&quot;,
    &quot;expires_in&quot;: 3600,
    &quot;refresh_token&quot;: &quot;43018382188f462f6b0e5784dd44c36f476ccce6&quot;,
    &quot;scope&quot;: null,
    &quot;token_type&quot;: &quot;Bearer&quot;
}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Failure&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;A failure can be of multiple reasons; it can be either&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Access Token Expired&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Value Missing&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;idType Mismatch&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;/ul&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;Please refer to &lt;a href=&quot;https://httpstatuses.com&quot;&gt;HTTP Status&lt;/a&gt; Codes for more information&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;pre class=&quot;fail&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-http&quot;&gt;HTTP/1.1 401 Unauthorized
Content-Type: application/json

{
    &quot;access_token&quot;: &quot;907c762e069589c2cd2a229cdae7b8778caa9f07&quot;,
    &quot;expires_in&quot;: 3600,
    &quot;refresh_token&quot;: &quot;43018382188f462f6b0e5784dd44c36f476ccce6&quot;,
    &quot;scope&quot;: null,
    &quot;token_type&quot;: &quot;Bearer&quot;
}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

      &lt;h3 id=&quot;search&quot;&gt;Search User&lt;/h3&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipisicing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua.&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-http&quot;&gt;POST /entity/user?_format=json HTTP/1.1
Host: dashboard.pegke.com/v1
Content-Type: application/json
Authorization: Bearer RvnIMUDspJs_RFFIKqWYF4zGMDJL9C4OrXHao3-mrZ8

{
  &quot;idType&quot;: &quot;mob&quot; // either mob, cid, email
  &quot;mob&quot;: 9826471001 // 10 Digit Phone number. must match with the value of &lt;strong&gt;idType&lt;/strong&gt;
  &quot;points&quot;: 10 // the points
}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

      &lt;h4 id=&quot;response-1&quot;&gt;Response&lt;/h4&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Success&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;pre class=&quot;success&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-http&quot;&gt;HTTP/1.1 200 OK
Content-Type: application/json

{
    &quot;access_token&quot;: &quot;907c762e069589c2cd2a229cdae7b8778caa9f07&quot;,
    &quot;expires_in&quot;: 3600,
    &quot;refresh_token&quot;: &quot;43018382188f462f6b0e5784dd44c36f476ccce6&quot;,
    &quot;scope&quot;: null,
    &quot;token_type&quot;: &quot;Bearer&quot;
}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Failure&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;A failure can be of multiple reasons; it can be either&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Access Token Expired&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Value Missing&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;idType Mismatch&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;/ul&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;Please refer to &lt;a href=&quot;https://httpstatuses.com&quot;&gt;HTTP Status&lt;/a&gt; Codes for more information&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;pre class=&quot;fail&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-http&quot;&gt;HTTP/1.1 401 Unauthorized
Content-Type: application/json

{
    &quot;access_token&quot;: &quot;907c762e069589c2cd2a229cdae7b8778caa9f07&quot;,
    &quot;expires_in&quot;: 3600,
    &quot;refresh_token&quot;: &quot;43018382188f462f6b0e5784dd44c36f476ccce6&quot;,
    &quot;scope&quot;: null,
    &quot;token_type&quot;: &quot;Bearer&quot;
}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

      &lt;h3 id=&quot;validate&quot;&gt;Validate a Redeem&lt;/h3&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipisicing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua.&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-http&quot;&gt;POST /entity/user?_format=json HTTP/1.1
Host: dashboard.pegke.com/v1
Content-Type: application/json
Authorization: Bearer RvnIMUDspJs_RFFIKqWYF4zGMDJL9C4OrXHao3-mrZ8

{
  &quot;idType&quot;: &quot;mob&quot; // either mob, cid, email
  &quot;mob&quot;: 9826471001 // 10 Digit Phone number. must match with the value of &lt;strong&gt;idType&lt;/strong&gt;
  &quot;points&quot;: 10 // the points
}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

      &lt;h4 id=&quot;response-2&quot;&gt;Response&lt;/h4&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Success&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;pre class=&quot;success&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-http&quot;&gt;HTTP/1.1 200 OK
Content-Type: application/json

{
    &quot;access_token&quot;: &quot;907c762e069589c2cd2a229cdae7b8778caa9f07&quot;,
    &quot;expires_in&quot;: 3600,
    &quot;refresh_token&quot;: &quot;43018382188f462f6b0e5784dd44c36f476ccce6&quot;,
    &quot;scope&quot;: null,
    &quot;token_type&quot;: &quot;Bearer&quot;
}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Failure&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;A failure can be of multiple reasons; it can be either&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Access Token Expired&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Value Missing&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;idType Mismatch&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;/ul&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;Please refer to &lt;a href=&quot;https://httpstatuses.com&quot;&gt;HTTP Status&lt;/a&gt; Codes for more information&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;pre class=&quot;fail&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-http&quot;&gt;HTTP/1.1 401 Unauthorized
Content-Type: application/json

{
    &quot;access_token&quot;: &quot;907c762e069589c2cd2a229cdae7b8778caa9f07&quot;,
    &quot;expires_in&quot;: 3600,
    &quot;refresh_token&quot;: &quot;43018382188f462f6b0e5784dd44c36f476ccce6&quot;,
    &quot;scope&quot;: null,
    &quot;token_type&quot;: &quot;Bearer&quot;
}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

      &lt;h3 id=&quot;shistory&quot;&gt;Store History&lt;/h3&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipisicing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat. Duis aute irure dolor in reprehenderit in voluptate velit esse cillum dolore eu fugiat nulla pariatur. Excepteur sint occaecat cupidatat non proident, sunt in culpa qui officia deserunt mollit anim id est laborum.&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipisicing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat. Duis aute irure dolor in reprehenderit in voluptate velit esse cillum dolore eu fugiat nulla pariatur. Excepteur sint occaecat cupidatat non proident, sunt in culpa qui officia deserunt mollit anim id est laborum.&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;h3 id=&quot;uhistory&quot;&gt;User History&lt;/h3&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipisicing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat. Duis aute irure dolor in reprehenderit in voluptate velit esse cillum dolore eu fugiat nulla pariatur. Excepteur sint occaecat cupidatat non proident, sunt in culpa qui officia deserunt mollit anim id est laborum.&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;div class=&quot;ui divider hidden&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;div class=&quot;ui divider horizontal header blue&quot;&gt;
        &lt;h2 id=&quot;rta&quot;&gt;Realtime Activity API&lt;/h2&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;h3 id=&quot;store&quot;&gt;Store Activity&lt;/h3&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipisicing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat. Duis aute irure dolor in reprehenderit in voluptate velit esse cillum dolore eu fugiat nulla pariatur. Excepteur sint occaecat cupidatat non proident, sunt in culpa qui officia deserunt mollit anim id est laborum.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;div class=&quot;four wide column mobile hidden&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;ui sticky&quot;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;ui vertical fluid menu hashnav&quot;&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;main item&quot; href=&quot;#web&quot;&gt;Web API&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;menu&quot;&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;item&quot; href=&quot;#auth&quot;&gt;Authenticate&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a class=&quot;item&quot; href=&quot;#give&quot;&gt;Give Loyalty Points&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a class=&quot;item&quot; href=&quot;#search&quot;&gt;Search User&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a class=&quot;item&quot; href=&quot;#validate&quot;&gt;Validate a Redeem&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a class=&quot;item&quot; href=&quot;#shistory&quot;&gt;Store History&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a class=&quot;item&quot; href=&quot;#uhistory&quot;&gt;User History&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;main item&quot; href=&quot;#rta&quot;&gt;Realtime Activity API&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;div class=&quot;menu&quot;&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;item&quot; href=&quot;#store&quot;&gt;Store Activity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;div class=&quot;ui segment&quot;&gt;
        &lt;h4&gt;Quick Links&lt;/h4&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;ui bulleted list&quot;&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;item&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://github.com/pegkeloyalty&quot;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;a class=&quot;item&quot; href=&quot;/about/brand-guidelines&quot;&gt;Brand Guidelines&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;a class=&quot;item&quot; href=&quot;/about/technology-stack&quot;&gt;Technology stack&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;a class=&quot;item&quot; href=&quot;/contact&quot;&gt;Support&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;a class=&quot;item&quot; href=&quot;/about/careers&quot;&gt;Join Our Team&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;a class=&quot;item&quot; href=&quot;/api/&quot;&gt;API&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;/api/faq&quot; class=&quot;item&quot;&gt;Developer FAQ&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;ui divider hidden&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;div class=&quot;ui blue small message&quot;&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;All API requests must be made over HTTPS. Calls made over plain HTTP will fail. API requests without authentication will also fail.&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;div class=&quot;ui segment&quot;&gt;
        &lt;h3&gt;References&lt;/h3&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;ui bulleted list&quot;&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc6750&quot; class=&quot;item&quot; title=&quot;The OAuth 2.0 Authorization Framework: Bearer Token Usage&quot;&gt;OAuth 2.0 Bearer Token Usage&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;/api/faq&quot; class=&quot;item&quot;&gt;Developer FAQ&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>https://pegke.com/api/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pegke.com/api/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Developer FAQ</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;ui text segment pegke&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;ui accordion&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;title&quot;&gt;
      &lt;i class=&quot;dropdown icon&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
      App token has expired!
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;content&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;transition hidden&quot;&gt;First, that is a good thing. Tokens are like cash, if you have it you can use it. You don&#39;t need to prove that token belongs to you, so don&#39;t let anyone steal your token. In order to lower the risk tokens should expire fairly quickly. If your token expires in 120s then it will be only usable during that window.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;title&quot;&gt;
      &lt;i class=&quot;dropdown icon&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
      What do I do if my token was expired?
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;content&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        Along with your access token, an authentication token is created. It&#39;s called the refresh token . It&#39;s a longer lived token, that it&#39;s associated to an access token and can be used to create a replica of your expired access token. You can then use that new access token normally.

        To use your refresh token you will need to make a request against /simple-oauth/refresh providing the header Authorization: Bearer {YOUR REFRESH TOKEN}. That will return a JSON document with the new token. That URL can only be accessed with your refresh token, even if your access token is still valid.
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;title&quot;&gt;
      &lt;i class=&quot;dropdown icon&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
      What do I do if my refresh token was also expired?
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;content&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        Then you will need to log into Drupal and go to your profile page to generate a new token from scratch. You can avoid this by refreshing your access token before your refresh token expires. This way you avoid the need to require the user to go to Drupal to create a new token.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
          Another way to mitigate this is to use longer expiration times in your tokens. This will work, but the the recommendation is to refresh your token in time.
        &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;ui divider hidden&quot;&gt;

  &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;ui text green segment pegke&quot;&gt;
  &lt;h3 class=&quot;ui header&quot;&gt;We Love Developers&lt;/h3&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    You&#39;ve came this far, we appreciate that... :)
  &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;div class=&quot;ui divider horizontal&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;ui huge heart rating&quot; data-rating=&quot;1&quot; data-max-rating=&quot;1&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;h4&gt;Quick Links&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;ui bulleted list&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a class=&quot;item&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://github.com/pegkeloyalty&quot;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;a class=&quot;item&quot; href=&quot;/about/brand-guidelines&quot;&gt;Brand Guidelines&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;a class=&quot;item&quot; href=&quot;/about/technology-stack&quot;&gt;Technology stack&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;a class=&quot;item&quot; href=&quot;/contact&quot;&gt;Support&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;a class=&quot;item&quot; href=&quot;/about/careers&quot;&gt;Join Our Team&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;a class=&quot;item&quot; href=&quot;/api/&quot;&gt;API&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;/api/faq&quot; class=&quot;item&quot;&gt;Developer FAQ&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;ui divider hidden&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>https://pegke.com/api/faq</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pegke.com/api/faq</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Customer Loyalty Program</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;why-a-customer-loyalty-program-&quot;&gt;Why a Customer Loyalty Program ?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Customers finding it difficult to stay loyal to your business? Tired of following a single brand that does not reward you for your loyalty? Enter the Pegke Customer Loyalty &amp;amp; Rewards Software that not only rewards the customers for their brand loyalty but also makes the customers stay loyal to their favorite franchises. Pegke is not just another app in the store, it is an easy-to-use software designed and shaped elegantly by Technopark engineers that is advantageous to both the business and customers. The software is sculpted in such a way that the user will find it easy to navigate and handle the loyalty program. After setting up their account, the business owners are able to set loyalty points for specific sales and are also able to reward customers based on their accumulated points and redeemable items. Additionally, the customers are also happy as they get rewarded for staying loyal to the business and Pegke makes the ‘staying loyal’ part easier for them as all these can be done in the comfort of their smartphones and tablets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By using the app, the business owners are able to analyze the sales and customers and therefore are able to modify their rewards program accordingly. The loyal customers are able to find and stay loyal to all their favorite businesses and franchises in a single place with the help of Pegke. Too good to be true? Start believing by downloading the Pegke app and by acquiring rewards in exchange for just your loyalty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;create-identity-through-customer-loyalty-program&quot;&gt;Create identity through Customer Loyalty Program&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Offering returning clients a rebate on administrations&lt;/strong&gt;
Everybody adores a decent arrangement. Subsequently, when a client comes back to you, it is a smart thought to remunerate them for returning. This doesn’t need to be an immense rebate; it can simply be a rate off of their bill.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Giving prizes for references&lt;/strong&gt;
Giving your present clients rewards for alluding different clients to you is yet another approach to demonstrate your present clients you admire their business.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Offering overhauls&lt;/strong&gt;
On your Facebook or Twitter page, you can post overhauls about your business and even your own life - on the off chance that you are agreeable with that. This will make your clients feel like they know you. They will have within scoop, an off camera take a gander at what you are managing on any given day.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Truly thinking about your clients&lt;/strong&gt;
Your clients will see through any fake representations on your part. In this manner, when you expect to manufacture associations with your clients, make sure that you really do think about their prosperity. By treating your clients well, you will be stunned at how willing they get to be to backing your business.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>https://pegke.com/customer-loyalty-program</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pegke.com/customer-loyalty-program</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What is Pegke?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Pegke is a Customer Loyalty &amp;amp; Retention Management Software, which integrates with merchant POS systems to give consumers a single identity to earn business-specific rewards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Pegke is a Customer Loyalty &amp;amp; Retention Management Software, which integrates with merchant POS systems to give consumers a single identity to earn business-specific rewards.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Best way to juggle money on things you love or on places you most often visit.  Pegke is an easy to use customer loyalty program or a reward point system, beneficial to both the merchant and the customer. Shops drive attention of customers through customer loyalty programs by offering fantastic ways to reward and say thank you to their customers. Customers are rewarded with points for each visit they make. More they visit the more points they collect. A best way to juggle your money at a place where you love to hangout. Collected points are redeemable as per the offers available at the stores.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>https://pegke.com/faq/what-is-pegke</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pegke.com/faq/what-is-pegke</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Retail Sector</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;ui basic fluid segment text&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;ui image right floated lazy&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.geekspeaktraining.com/coaching/images/pages/how-we-can-help-you.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;We believe that business objectives and users’ goals should be treated as equals, and that doing this creates winning brand experiences.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Our opinion is that insight and understanding are crucial for achieving success but also know that, on occasions, unnecessarily bloated research projects can delay progress. To this end we have made a conscious effort to be able to provide insight for businesses of any size in an agile timeframe.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h2 id=&quot;how-we-can-help-you&quot;&gt;How we can help you&lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;If you can’t confidently answer yes to all of the following questions, you would benefit from our services.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Have you defined your audience segments?&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Have you created audience personas?&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Have you identified your users red routes (key tasks)?&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Do you use a user-centered approach?&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Do you conduct regular user testing?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ul&gt;

  &lt;h2 id=&quot;optimise-and-refine&quot;&gt;Optimise and refine&lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;We help businesses identify and fix problems with their existing user experiences and work with them to set up methods to measure, monitor and iterate based on data from three key usability metrics – effectiveness, efficiency and satisfaction.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Do you monitor user satisfaction?&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Do you monitor the effectiveness and efficiency of your digital services?&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Are you happy that your user experience can’t be improved?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>https://pegke.com/business/retail-sector</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pegke.com/business/retail-sector</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Consumer Goods Sector</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;ui basic fluid segment text&quot;&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipisicing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat. Duis aute irure dolor in reprehenderit in voluptate velit esse cillum dolore eu fugiat nulla pariatur. Excepteur sint occaecat cupidatat non proident, sunt in culpa qui officia deserunt mollit anim id est laborum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>https://pegke.com/business/consumer-goods-sector</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pegke.com/business/consumer-goods-sector</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Banking &amp; Financial</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;ui basic fluid segment text&quot;&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;At a time of unprecedented structural change in the financial services industry, banks and credit unions are contending with increasing challenges, including post-crisis regulations, a more demanding consumer and new competition from inside and outside the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;blockquote&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Organizations are responding by making significant investments in core systems &amp;gt; replacement, digital channels and data analytics to ensure their ongoing
competitiveness.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/blockquote&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;While compliance with new regulations and new competitors remain a major challenge, maintaining customer loyalty is considered to be the financial industry’s biggest challenge, according to a study by Temenos. Cited by 30% of global senior bankers, there is concern that more empowered and better informed customers may begin to switch providers in greater numbers.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Temenos’ 7th Annual Survey of Challenges, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.temenos.com/en-us/market-insight/universal-insight/temenos-7th-annual-survey-of-the-financial-services-sector/&quot;&gt;Priorities and Trends in the Financial Services Sector&lt;/a&gt; found that the industry overall views their biggest threat as being technology vendors, such as Apple and Google (cited by 23% of respondents). In comparison, the retail bank and credit union sector found existing large incumbents and new bank entrants to be the biggest threat.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h2 id=&quot;two-major-findings&quot;&gt;Two major findings&lt;/h2&gt;

  &lt;h3 id=&quot;a-surge-in-mobile-banking&quot;&gt;1. A surge in mobile banking&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p class=&quot;ui image left floated lazy&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/banking_channel_mix.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Mobile banking via smartphone or tablet is coming on strong in many countries. In the US, mobile usage jumped to 32% of customers from 21% in 2011. Usage in 2012 ranges from 47% of respondents in South Korea to 37% in India to 16% in Germany.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Mobile banking is more likely to increase a US customer’s likelihood of recommending the bank than any other channel interaction. US customers especially love sophisticated features such as remote deposit capture (a digital image of an endorsed check), and they value the convenience of mobile devices for straightforward tasks such as checking a balance.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;In most European and Asian countries, customers cite online tools and transactions as having the strongest inﬂuence on their recommending a bank.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The future is here and its name is “omnichannel”&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;If banks can take out costs in the processes that handle routine transactions, they will be able to serve mass segments more profitably and invest disproportionately in high-margin services for the afﬂuent. The way to accomplish this is through an omnichannel approach—integrating disparate digital and physical channels into a single, seamless experience—tailored to address the priorities of each customer segment.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class=&quot;ui image fluid lazy&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/img/customer-loyalty-in-retail-banking-2012-fig-10_full.gif&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;In the omnichannel world, branches play a different role: more as product showrooms, sales centers and venues for expert financial advice on complex matters, and less as transaction mills. Light but sturdy branches include more self-service terminals for routine tasks or product application forms and interactive tutorials.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Loyalty trends worldwide&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;When it comes to loyalty rankings, it’s all relative. As banks review their Net Promoter scores, those with high scores may be tempted to compare across markets and declare themselves “best national bank” or “best credit union” globally.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;That would be misleading. Different countries exhibit structural differences in loyalty scores. We consistently find easier grading in some markets (the US and Mexico, among others) and very tough grading in others (the UK and France). Even within the US, we find variance among regions.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class=&quot;ui image fluid lazy&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.bain.com/Images/customer-loyalty-in-retail-banking-2012-map_full.gif&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h3 id=&quot;priorities-of-high-value-customer-segments&quot;&gt;2. Priorities of high-value customer segments&lt;/h3&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;While the pace of regulatory change has abated somewhat, complying with complex new rules continues to require operational adjustment and high financial and human commitment. The challenge of complying with new regulations is considered much greater in the US and western Europe, where governments have potentially overcompensated for a perceived lack of regulation before the financial crisis.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Private wealth management (PWM) and the universal banking sectors viewed regulation as their biggest threat in 36% and 28% of cases, respectively, caused by sector specific regulations that are onerous.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h4 id=&quot;other-concerns&quot;&gt;Other concerns&lt;/h4&gt;

  &lt;h5 id=&quot;product-innovation-prioritization&quot;&gt;Product Innovation Prioritization&lt;/h5&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Correlating with the challenges of increased competition and consumer demands, product innovation was cited by 24% of the senior banker respondents to the Tememos survey, with 26% of retail bankers citing product innovation as their number one priority.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class=&quot;ui image left floated lazy&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://thefinancialbrand.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/09/s_investment_priorities_9-28-2014-565x445.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;The picture is similar with investment in digital channels, with 18% of overall respondents and 20% of retail banking respondents mentioning digital channels as top priority. Interestingly, 22% of private wealth management sector respondents said investing in mobile channels was their top priority, suggesting the importance of younger investors.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Not to be forgotten, investing in branches remains a priority (7% vs. 12% in 2012), indicating that retail banks are updating branch formats, increasing investment in new branch technology while converting physical facilities to centers for sales and advice as opposed to transactions.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h5 id=&quot;it-spending-explodes&quot;&gt;IT Spending Explodes&lt;/h5&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Aligning with other studies, the Telemos research found that 67% of respondents expected higher IT budgets in 2014 and just 11% anticipated their IT budget to shrink, giving a net positive delta of 56%, higher than in 2013 (53%) and in 2008 (46%).&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;The trend illustrates how all banks, regardless of sector or geographical region recognize the priority of investing in IT to sustain competitiveness in the digital age. Real-time core banking system renewal built around customer records and not products, was cited as the number one IT investment priority for banks in 2014.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;The second biggest priority for IT spending, cited by 23% of respondents, was digital channels, with the single biggest area of investment being mobile apps for tablets and smartphones, cited by 32% of respondents. Overall, 17% of respondents were directing most of their mobile bank spending to building out basic services, such as balance requests and transfers, illustrating the game of catch up that many banks are faced with.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://thefinancialbrand.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/09/planned_mobile_banking_investments_9-28-2014.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>https://pegke.com/business/banking-financial-loyalty</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pegke.com/business/banking-financial-loyalty</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Terms and Conditions</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;general&quot;&gt;1. General&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During the length of the Merchant Agreement, Pegke Rewards will provide the Pegke Rewards services and/or programs (collectively, “Pegke Rewards Programs”) described in the Merchant Agreement separately executed by you, together with all exhibits attached thereto (the “Merchant Agreement”). In the event of any inconsistency among terms and conditions of the Merchant Agreement and these Terms and Conditions (collectively, sometimes referred to herein as the “Agreement”), the order of control shall be: (i) these Terms and Conditions, (ii) the Merchant Agreement, and (iii) any other exhibits, addenda or attachments to these Terms and Conditions including any links contained in the Merchant Agreement or these Terms and Conditions, which are incorporated by reference herein. Any capitalized terms that are not defined in these Terms and Conditions have the meanings ascribed to them in the Merchant Agreement. For purposes of clarity, these Terms and Conditions are incorporated by reference into the Merchant Agreement executed by you, and, together with the Merchant Agreement and all attachments thereto, govern your use of all Pegke Rewards Programs and services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;intellectual-property-rights&quot;&gt;2. Intellectual Property Rights.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(i) Pegke Rewards is the sole and exclusive owner of all right, title and interest in and to any data provided to Pegke Rewards by your customers or any end user to Pegke Rewards in connection with the Pegke Rewards Programs, including without limitation all e-mail and/or other contact information (“Customer Data”). As such, you shall not, unless the applicable customer has separately taken all steps necessary to opt in to provide contact information to you, be provided with or otherwise have access to the Customer Data.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(ii) Pegke Rewards owns all right, title and interest in and to the Pegke Rewards Programs (which include, for purposes of clarity, all software and/or mobile applications related thereto) including, without limitation, any intellectual property rights and any improvements, modifications, enhancements or refinements thereto. Except as set forth in the Agreement, all rights not expressly granted to you are reserved. You agree not to decipher, decompile, disassemble, reconstruct, translate, reverse engineer, or discover any of the Pegke Rewards Programs, intellectual property or ideas, algorithms, file formats, programming, or interoperability interfaces underlying or such intellectual property.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(iii) Pegke Rewards hereby grants to you a limited, non-transferable, non-exclusive, revocable license to access and use Pegke Rewards’s hosted Merchant Web Portal (the “Portal”) for internal business purposes so long as your account with Pegke Rewards remains current and active. If Pegke Rewards provides you with a password to access the Portal, you are solely responsible for protecting the password and for any authorized or unauthorized use made of the password. The Portal, and all source code, object code, software, copyrights and other intellectual property associated therewith, are and shall remain the sole and exclusive property of Pegke Rewards. You shall refrain from permitting any third party to use your password or otherwise access the Portal. Pegke Rewards shall have the right to terminate the license granted hereby immediately in the event that you have breached any terms or conditions set forth in the Agreement or your Pegke Rewards account is otherwise terminated for any reason.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(iv) Without limiting any of Pegke Rewards’s rights set forth in the Agreement, Pegke Rewards reserves the right, in its sole discretion but without any obligation on its part, to reject, remove, delete and/or cancel any information or content displayed or posted on any tablet, the Pegke Rewards website, any portion of the Pegke Rewards Program, and/or within any print materials, including without limitation any information and/or content that, in Pegke Rewards’s view, contains content or links which do not meet Pegke Rewards’s specifications or requirements. In addition, Pegke Rewards shall be entitled, in its sole discretion and without notice to any party, to redesign and/or modify all or any portion of the Pegke Rewards Program (including without limitation any mobile application and/or software) at any time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;restrictions&quot;&gt;3. Restrictions.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You: (i) will use the Pegke Rewards Programs solely for your internal business purposes; and (ii) will not, for yourself, any of your affiliates or any third party (a) sell, rent, lease, license or sublicense, assign, distribute, or transfer the Pegke Rewards Programs, (b) modify, change, alter, create derivative works of, decipher, decompile, disassemble, reconstruct, translate, reverse engineer, or discover any source code of the underlying ideas, algorithms, file formats, programming, or interoperability interfaces of the Pegke Rewards Programs, (c) copy any tangible versions of the Pegke Rewards Programs, or (d) remove from any of the Pegke Rewards Programs any language or designation indicating the confidential nature thereof or the proprietary rights of Pegke Rewards. In addition, you will not export, re-export or permit any third party to export or re-export, directly or indirectly, the Pegke Rewards Programs where such export or re-export is prohibited by applicable law without appropriate licenses and clearances. Pegke Rewards retains the right, in its sole discretion but without any obligation on the part of Pegke Rewards to monitor or evaluate any communications, to approve, modify or refuse any Pegke Rewards-related communications or proposed communications or messages to your customers or any Pegke Rewards end users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;fees-pricing-and-payment-terms-taxes&quot;&gt;4. Fees; Pricing and Payment Terms; Taxes.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(i) Pegke Rewards’s current fees for the Pegke Rewards Programs and its services are set forth in the Merchant Agreement. Pegke Rewards reserves the right to amend the fees payable for the Pegke Rewards Programs at any time upon thirty (30) days’ prior notice to you; provided, however, that such amendment to the fees will not be applicable until the beginning of the next Subscription Period.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(ii) When you provide your payment information to Pegke Rewards, you are providing Pegke Rewards with an authorization to process any and all payments as outlined in this Agreement. In certain instances, the payment processing may not occur immediately, and your payment may show as “pending” during this time period. In addition, Pegke Rewards may request an authorization for the amount of your anticipated transaction in advance and may estimate the final value of the transaction, which may be more than the amount of the actual transaction. Pegke Rewards will release any funds authorized in excess of the amount of the actual transaction at the time the transaction settles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(iii) You will be responsible for any sales, use, value-added or import taxes, customs duties or similar taxes assessed in accordance with applicable law with respect to the provision of the Pegke Rewards Programs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(iv) Notwithstanding anything herein to the contrary, Pegke Rewards, in its sole discretion, may suspend or terminate the Agreement and corresponding access and right to use all or any portion of the Pegke Rewards Programs, at any time, upon electronic or other notice to you, if you have not paid all amounts due on or before the payment due date, or for any other breaches of the Merchant Agreement, these Terms and Conditions, or any other exhibits, addenda or attachments to these Terms and Conditions including any links contained in the Merchant Agreement or these Terms and Conditions, which are incorporated by reference herein. You are responsible for amounts that remain outstanding as of the date of such termination including early cancellation fees. You agree to pay reasonable attorneys’ fees and court costs incurred by Pegke Rewards to collect any unpaid amounts owed by you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(v) Pegke Rewards will repair or replace damaged tablets due to normal wear and year or any hardware/software malfunction at no cost to any merchant in good standing. A merchant in good standing is primarily defined as having no outstanding balance due to Pegke Rewards, but may be defined by other criteria as specified by Pegke Rewards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(vi) Should your Merchant Agreement indicate a seasonal term, your contract will be extended by the number of months which billing is paused for seasonality, as indicated on the Agreement. All Pegke Rewards equipment will remain the responsibility of the merchant during entire term of the Agreement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;term-termination-survival&quot;&gt;5. Term; Termination; Survival.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Pegke Rewards solution term, as further described below, is effective upon the earlier of the arrival date or estimated arrival date of the solution as stated within the Merchant Agreement. All other subsequent changes or modifications to the merchant agreement are effective upon the completion of the merchant purchase order. You may amend your contract to include additional Pegke Rewards features through your Web Command Center. When you make changes through your Web Command Center, you are providing explicit authorization for Pegke Rewards to process payment on your existing Pegke Rewards account and method of payment without any further authorization necessary from you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Agreement will remain in full force specified in the Merchant Agreement. At the end of any Subscription Plan, unless you select a new Subscription Plan, your Subscription Plan will automatically renew on a month–to–month Subscription Plan at the then-current rates. Effective January 1, 2015, new agreements and/or subscriptions may automatically renew for successive 1-year terms upon expiration of the initial term of any Subscription Plan at the then-current standard rates until such time as either party provides written notice of termination to the other party, in accordance with terms below. Current fees will be charged to the payment method on file unless Pegke Rewards is otherwise notified of a cancellation in writing. Although Pegke Rewards may choose to send a reminder email prior to charging a customer for a renewal fee, Pegke Rewards is not responsible for notifying a customer of this automated renewal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A merchant may cancel its subscription, thereby terminating this Agreement, solely in accordance with the following cancellation policies:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Money Back Guarantee – If your Merchant Agreement specifies that you are entitled to a “30 day Money Back Guarantee” you shall, by providing written termination notice to Pegke Rewards within thirty (30) days of the Installation Date, be entitled to have the Pegke Rewards Kit uninstalled. In order to qualify for your Money–Back–Guarantee, we simply require that you speak to your Merchant Success Manager to set up your program and enroll a minimum of 5 customers during the Money–Back–Guarantee period. If you do not meet these qualifications you will be charged a restocking fee of $50 upon cancellation. Within thirty (30) days of Pegke Rewards’s receipt of the Pegke Rewards Kit, Pegke Rewards will refund you any money collected for the initial monthly subscription fee in the same manner in which the initial fee was paid. All Onboarding, Activation, or Setup fees are non-refundable. If, after thirty (30) days from the Installation Date and prior to the subsequent Subscription Period, you desire to terminate the Pegke Rewards Program, you agree to pay an early cancellation fee equal to six (6) months of your monthly subscription fee, as well as a $50 restocking fee via the credit card or ACH on file with Pegke Rewards. If you subscribe to a variable subscription fee plan, your early cancellation fee is equal to (6) months at the most recent monthly billed rate along with a $50 restocking fee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Renewal – At the end of any Subscription Plan, unless you select a new Subscription plan, your Subscription Plan will automatically be renewed on an annual or monthly (as applicable) basis at the then-current standard rates. Current fees will be charged to the credit card or ACH on file unless Pegke Rewards is otherwise notified of a cancellation in writing. Customers renewed on a monthly basis must provide written cancellation notice at least sixty (60) days prior to the beginning of the next monthly or annual term (as applicable). Customers renewed on an annual basis must provide written cancellation notice sixty (60) days prior to or within the first thirty (30) days of their renewal period. Although Pegke Rewards may choose to send a reminder email prior to charging a customer for a renewal fee, Pegke Rewards is not responsible for notifying a customer of this automated renewal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Subscription Cancellation within the Contract Term – Customers enrolled in Monthly or Annual subscription plans shall provide at least sixty (60) days’ written cancellation notice. If, prior to the subsequent Subscription Period, you desire to terminate the Pegke Rewards Program, You agree to pay an early cancellation fee equal to six (6) months of your monthly subscription fee, as well as a $50 restocking fee via the credit card or ACH on file with Pegke Rewards. If you subscribe to a variable subscription fee plan, your early cancellation fee is equal to six (6) months at the most recent monthly billed rate along with a $50 restocking fee. You will not be entitled to any refund of any pre-paid or prior subscription payments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other Events – Each party shall have the right to terminate the Agreement upon written notice to the other party: (i) upon the institution of insolvency, receivership or bankruptcy proceedings or any other proceedings for the settlement of debts of the other party that is not otherwise dismissed within sixty (60) days of such institution; (ii) upon the making of an assignment for the benefit of creditors by the other party; or (iii) upon the dissolution of the other party. Notwithstanding the foregoing, Pegke Rewards may terminate the Agreement and/or your access to one or all Pegke Rewards Programs in the event you fail to remain current in all fees due and owing to Pegke Rewards or in the event you breach any of your obligations under the Agreement. Pegke Rewards will cease to collect the monthly subscription fee at the point in time in which Pegke Rewards has received your returned Pegke Rewards Kit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the event of any termination of the Agreement or any Pegke Rewards Program, Pegke Rewards shall be entitled to send e-mail and/or other communications to some or all of your loyalty program members, notifying each such member of your termination of the Pegke Rewards Program. In addition to the foregoing permissible e-mail, Pegke Rewards shall be entitled to take other actions, at its discretion, to assist your loyalty program members in protecting the points earned within the Pegke Rewards Program and providing them an opportunity to redeem points earned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition, all items in the Pegke Rewards Kit must be returned to Pegke Rewards in specified return packaging provided by Pegke Rewards. If you were not previously provided with specified return packaging, Pegke Rewards will provide you with specified return packaging at no cost to you, otherwise you will be charged for packaging materials. You are responsible for all return shipping charges and for any damage incurred in the shipping process. If any item in the Pegke Rewards Kit is not returned, Pegke Rewards will charge you for the cost of the item not returned. Pegke Rewards will prorate the last monthly subscription fee based on the date the Pegke Rewards Kit is received by Pegke Rewards. You may be required to fill out an exit survey in order to complete any cancellation request. Pegke Rewards may refuse to accept the return of its equipment until the exit survey is completed. If You do not complete the exit survey in a timely fashion, You may be charged a fee for missing equipment until the exit survey is completed. Any provision of the Agreement which contemplates performance or observance subsequent to any termination or expiration of the Agreement shall survive any termination or expiration of the Agreement and continue in full force and effect. Upon expiration or termination of this agreement all items in the Pegke Rewards Kit must be returned to Pegke Rewards within 14 days. If the tablet is lost or not returned within 14 days, you will be charged a penalty fee to cover the tablet equipment costs as well as a non–refundable late fee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;representations-and-warranties-disclaimer&quot;&gt;6. Representations and Warranties; Disclaimer.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(i) Pegke Rewards warrants that Pegke Rewards has the authority to enter into this Agreement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(ii) You represent, warrant and covenant to Pegke Rewards that: (a) you have the authority to enter into this Agreement; (b) you will take proper care of the Pegke Rewards Kit and/or all equipment provided by Pegke Rewards to you and maintain all such equipment in good working order; (c) you will only use the Pegke Rewards Programs for lawful purposes and will not violate any law of any country or the intellectual property rights of any third party; and (d) you will not use any Pegke Rewards Program to send any e-mail or other communications which violate any applicable regulation, rule, industry protocol or law (including, without limitation, the CAN-SPAM Act).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(iii) EXCEPT AS SPECIFICALLY PROVIDED IN THIS SECTION 6, Pegke Rewards EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF QUALITY, ACCURACY, MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN ADDITION, Pegke Rewards DOES NOT MAKE ANY REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES AS TO ANY MINIMUM LEVEL OF UPTIME FOR THE Pegke Rewards PROGRAM OR THE RESULTS THAT YOU MAY ACHIEVE ON ACCOUNT USING ANY Pegke Rewards PROGRAM OR SERVICE. TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, YOU EXPRESSLY AGREE THAT THE USE OF Pegke Rewards PROGRAMS OR SERVICES AND THE INTERNET IS AT YOUR SOLE RISK. Pegke Rewards PROGRAMS AND SERVICES ARE PROVIDED ON AN “AS IS” AND “AS AVAILABLE” BASIS, AND UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES SHALL Pegke Rewards BE LIABLE TO YOU OR ANY OTHER PARTY ON ACCOUNT OF ANY DOWNTIME WITHIN ANY Pegke Rewards PLATFORM OR APPLICATION. YOU HEREBY ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU ARE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR OBTAINING AND/OR PROVIDING INTERNET SERVICE TO ALL LOCATIONS IN WHICH THE Pegke Rewards PROGRAMS ARE TO OPERATE.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;confidential-information&quot;&gt;7. Confidential Information.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Any information that a receiving party knows or has reason to know (either because such information is marked or otherwise identified by the disclosing party orally or in writing as confidential or proprietary, has commercial value, or because it is not generally known in the relevant trade or industry) is “Confidential Information” of the disclosing party and will remain the sole property of the disclosing party. Such Confidential Information includes but is not limited to data, information (including personally identifiable information), ideas, materials, specifications, procedures, schedules, software, technical processes and formulas, source code, product designs, sales, cost and other unpublished financial information, product and business plans, advertising revenues, usage rates, advertising relationships, projections, marketing data and other similar information provided by a party. For avoidance of doubt, Customer Data shall be deemed Confidential Information of Pegke Rewards. Each party agrees that it will not disclose, use, modify, copy, reproduce or otherwise divulge such Confidential Information to any third party without the prior written approval of the disclosing party except that the receiving party shall have the right to disclose such Confidential Information to the extent required by applicable law or to the directors, officers or employees of the receiving party who have a need to know such Confidential Information in order to perform its obligations under the Agreement and to the extent such directors, officers or employees are subject to obligations of confidentiality and non-disclosure that are substantially similar to the obligations set forth in the Agreement. The prohibitions contained in this Section will not apply to information (i) already lawfully known to the receiving party prior to disclosure by the disclosing party; (ii) independently developed by the receiving party without access to or use of the disclosing party’s Confidential Information; (iii) disclosed in published materials; (iv) generally known to the public; or (v) lawfully obtained from any third party. In addition, a party will not be considered to have breached its obligations under the Agreement to the extent Confidential Information is required to be disclosed by any governmental authority, provided that, to the extent legally practicable, the receiving party advises the disclosing party prior to making such disclosure in order that the disclosing party may object to such disclosure, take action to ensure confidential treatment of the Confidential Information, or take such other action as it considers appropriate to protect the Confidential Information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;dispute-resolution-governing-law&quot;&gt;8. Dispute Resolution; Governing Law.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the event of a reward dispute or mistake between a Merchant and User, Pegke Rewards may in its sole discretion and without liability of any kind unilaterally make adjustments to User reward points (it being understood that Pegke Rewards shall not be (i) obligated to make any such adjustment or otherwise get involved with or provide any assistance towards resolving any such dispute, or (ii) be liable to any party for any damages, expenses or liabilities arising out of any such dispute). To the extent any disputes arise under the Agreement or otherwise between the parties, the parties will first attempt in good faith to resolve their dispute informally. If any dispute arises out of or in relation to this Agreement which cannot be amicably resolved between the Parties by mutual consultation the jurisdiction of the Court shall be any court in Thiruvananthapuram (or Trivandrum), Kerala, India.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;indemnification&quot;&gt;9. Indemnification.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will defend, indemnify, and hold Pegke Rewards and its affiliates and their respective directors, officers, employees, agents and representatives harmless from and against any third party suit, proceeding, assertion against any damages, judgments, liability, costs and expenses (including without limitation any reasonable attorneys’ fees) incurred arising from your breach of this Agreement, your negligence or misconduct, any dispute you may have with any other party in connection with any Pegke Rewards Program or otherwise related in any way to any Pegke Rewards Program, your unauthorized use or misuse of the Pegke Rewards Programs or any unauthorized combination of any Pegke Rewards Program with any hardware, software, products, data or other materials not specified or provided by Pegke Rewards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;limitation-of-liability&quot;&gt;10. Limitation of Liability.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pegke Rewards’s aggregate liability for all claims (including claims for indemnification of third party damages) arising out of the Agreement, whether in contract, tort or otherwise, will not exceed the amount of fees paid by you to Pegke Rewards under the Agreement during the twelve (12) months preceding the date on which the applicable claim occurred. To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, in no event will Pegke Rewards be liable for any loss of business profits, business interruption, loss of data or any special, indirect, exemplary, incidental or consequential damages arising from or in relation to the Agreement or the use of the Services or any Pegke Rewards Program, however caused and regardless of theory of liability. In addition, Pegke Rewards will not be liable for damage (physical or otherwise) incurred by you upon any asset or property from the installation or removal of any Pegke Rewards product or add-on in-store and will not be responsible for replacement or cost of repair if damages occur. This limitation will apply even if such damages were foreseeable and you have been advised or are aware of the possibility of such damages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;notice&quot;&gt;11. Notice.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Except where explicitly provided otherwise herein, any notice required or permitted hereunder will be delivered to the contact person listed on the Order Information as follows (with notice deemed given as indicated): (i) by personal delivery when delivered personally; (ii) by established overnight courier upon written verification of receipt; (iii) by facsimile transmission when receipt is confirmed orally; (iv) by certified or registered mail, return receipt requested, upon verification of receipt; or (v) by electronic delivery when receipt is confirmed orally.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;assignment&quot;&gt;12. Assignment.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You may not, without the prior written consent of Pegke Rewards, assign the Agreement, in whole or in part, either voluntarily or by operation of law, and any attempt to do so will be a material default of the Agreement and will be void; provided, however, that in the event of a sale of substantially all of your assets or equity to a third party or any merger of your entity with an into a third party, this Agreement shall be deemed, without any further action on the part of any party, to automatically be assigned to and assumed by the acquirer in such transaction and as such, shall be binding on such acquirer. The Agreement will be binding upon and will inure to the benefit of the respective parties hereto, their respective successors in interest, legal representatives, heirs and assigns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;no-third-party-beneficiaries&quot;&gt;13. No Third Party Beneficiaries.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Agreement is solely for the benefit of the parties and their successors and permitted assigns, and does not confer any rights or remedies on any other person or entity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;amendment-waiver&quot;&gt;14. Amendment; Waiver.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This Agreement may be changed by Pegke Rewards upon posting an updated version of the Agreement at Pegke Rewards’s website and/or within the applicable Pegke Rewards Program, any such change to become effective 10 business days after posting such updated version of the Agreement as described above. The failure of either party to exercise or enforce any of its rights under the Agreement will not act as a waiver of subsequent breaches and the waiver of any breach will not act as a waiver of subsequent breaches.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;severability&quot;&gt;15. Severability.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If any provision of the Agreement is held by a court or other tribunal of competent jurisdiction to be unenforceable, that provision will be enforced to the maximum extent permissible under applicable law and the other provisions of the Agreement will remain in full force and effect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;force-majeure&quot;&gt;16. Force Majeure.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Neither party shall be liable to the other if such party is prevented from performing any of its obligations under the Agreement (excluding fee payment obligations) due to any cause beyond the party’s reasonable control including, without limitation, an act of God, fire, flood, explosion, terrorism, war, embargo, government regulation, civil or military authority, acts or omissions of carriers, transmitters, providers, or acts of vandals, or hackers. The time for that party’s performance will be extended for the period of the delay or failure to perform due to such occurrence, except that you will not be excused from the payment of any sums of money owed by you to Pegke Rewards provided prior to the force majeure event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;independent-contractor&quot;&gt;17. Independent Contractor.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Agreement will not be construed as creating or constituting a partnership, joint venture, or agency relationship between the parties. Neither party will have the power to bind the other or incur obligations on the other’s behalf without the other’s prior written consent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;compliance-with-laws&quot;&gt;18. Compliance with Laws.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each party will comply with all applicable laws, regulations, and ordinances relating to their performance hereunder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;entire-agreement&quot;&gt;19. Entire Agreement.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Agreement (including, without limitation, the Merchant Agreement and these Merchant Terms) constitute the entire agreement between Pegke Rewards and you with respect to the subject matter hereof and all prior oral or written agreements, representations or statements with respect to such subject matter are superseded hereby.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;goal-gradient-loyalty-participation&quot;&gt;20. Goal Gradient Loyalty Participation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pegke Rewards may, at its sole discretion from time to time, elect to make point adjustments for first-time member visits (such as, by way of example, offering members the opportunity to earn extra points in connection with the first visit to a given Merchant location). These adjustments are intended to encourage greater follow-up participation to your program. This feature is automatically enabled with the onboarding of your loyalty program; provided, however, that you may elect to opt out of this program by providing written notice of such opt-out to Pegke Rewards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;campaign-terms-of-use&quot;&gt;21. Campaign Terms of Use&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The following terms shall, in addition to all of the other terms set forth in this Agreement, govern your use of Pegke Rewards’s “Campaign” platform (the “Campaign Platform”), which, at a general level, allows you to communicate with Pegke Rewards members.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;General Rules
You shall, as a condition to making any use of the Campaign Platform, be required to follow these rules:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;You won’t send Spam! While you are responsible for making yourself of aware of current anti-SPAM and similar regulations that may be in effect from time to time, as a general rule, you should assume that if you send people mass email without their permission, you’re spamming.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;You won’t violate Pegke Rewards’s Acceptable Use guidelines, established below, as they may be in effect from time to time, which is part of this Agreement. If you violate any of these rules, Pegke Rewards, in addition to any other rights or remedies that Pegke Rewards may have hereunder or otherwise, may suspend or terminate your account.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;In the event you have purchased a subscription which allows unlimited use of Campaign Platform, to the extent that Pegke Rewards, in its sole discretion, determines that you are abusing the Campaign Platform, violating any law or regulation, violating the CAN-SPAM Act or any other e-mail regulation or otherwise abusing or misusing the Campaign Platform in any way, Pegke Rewards shall, in addition to any other remedies available to Pegke Rewards in this Agreement and/or at law, be entitled to unilaterally adjust your allowed use of the product.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Membership Status Programs
You hereby agree and acknowledge that Pegke Rewards may, from time to time, offer and administer a program currently referred to as the “Membership Status” program. Pursuant to such program, Pegke Rewards members that are sufficiently active using the Pegke Rewards Programs can achieve various levels of status. Pegke Rewards shall have sole discretion in determining the activity required to obtain each of the status levels within the Membership Status program from time to time. Pegke Rewards members that have achieved any such level of status may be entitled to receive discounts on points and/or other benefits across the entire Pegke Rewards network, including without limitation at each of your locations. You hereby agree to honor all such discounts and recognize such status, except to the extent you have opted out of participation in the Pegke Rewards Membership Status program by written notice.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;compliance-with-laws-1&quot;&gt;Compliance with Laws&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You represent and warrant that your use of the Campaign Platform will comply with all applicable laws and regulations. You are responsible for determining whether Pegke Rewards’s services are suitable for you to use in light of any regulations such HIPAA, GLB, EU Data Privacy Laws and/or other laws. If you are subject to regulations (such as HIPAA) and you use the Campaign Platform or any other Pegke Rewards service, then Pegke Rewards will not be liable if any such service does not meet those requirements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;acceptable-use&quot;&gt;Acceptable Use&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You shall refrain from using the Campaign Platform to send anything offensive, to promote anything illegal, or to harass anyone. Not in limitation of the foregoing, you may not send:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Pornography or other sexually explicit Emails&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Emails offering to sell illegal goods or services&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Emails that violate CAN-SPAM Laws or any other applicable laws or regulations&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Acceptable Use – Prohibited Actions
Pegke Rewards works hard to keep its system clean, but Pegke Rewards also counts on its customers to pitch in. As such, you may not:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Send Spam (as noted above).&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Share your password.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Use any of the Campaign Platform to create a competing product.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Import or incorporate any of this information into any lists, emails or uploads to our servers: Social Security numbers, passwords, security credentials, or sensitive personal information of any kind.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Send any messages through the Campaign Platform that are not appropriate for its intended use.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Use an outside unsubscribe process.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>https://pegke.com/about/terms-conditions</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pegke.com/about/terms-conditions</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Privacy Policy</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;ui text pegke&quot;&gt;

  &lt;h2 id=&quot;importance-of-your-privacy&quot;&gt;Importance of Your Privacy.&lt;/h2&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;At Pegke, your privacy is of great importance to us. We understand that you entrust
us with certain private information to help us provide various products and services.
In exchange for your trust, you expect and deserve our commitment to treat your
information with respect and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
Rest assured that we will protect your privacy. Under no circumstances will Pegke
sell or share any personal information about you to or with any person or organization
except&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;as authorized by you,&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;as described in the relevant portion of Pegke’s Website (the “Website”)&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;in connection with providing various products and/or services to you (the “Services”),&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;to the extent you make any use of Pegke’s mobile software application commonly referred to
 as “Pegke Rewards” or any other Pegke mobile application (the “Application”),
 to merchants with which Pegke has a business relationship,&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;as may be required by law or court order, or&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;as otherwise set forth herein.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;The Privacy Policy below describes the standards we adhere to in handling information
about you and any personal information you submit through the Website and/or the Application.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Please read this privacy policy carefully before submitting any information to
pegke or through any pegke software or mobile application. by submitting any information
you are acknowledging that you have read and understand this policy and that you
agree to be bound by its terms. if you do not agree to be bound by the terms of this
privacy policy, simply exit this page and/or the application without accessing or
using any of our services.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h3 id=&quot;a-special-note-about-children&quot;&gt;A Special Note About Children.&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Children are not eligible to use our Services and we ask that minors
(under the age of 13) do not submit any personal information to us or use the
Services. Pegke does not collect or maintain information from those actually known
to be under the age of 13, and no part of Pegke’s website, the Application or
Services is structured to attract anyone under the age of 13. Other age restrictions
may be set forth in Pegke’s Terms of Use from time to time.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h3 id=&quot;important-categories-of-information-for-you-to-know&quot;&gt;Important Categories of Information for you to Know:&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Who we are&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Information we may collect at the Website or through the Application&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;How your information is used&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Altering the information you submit through the Website and/or Application&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;

  &lt;h4 id=&quot;who-we-are&quot;&gt;1. Who We Are.&lt;/h4&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Pegke operates a website located at www.pegke.com and the Application through which certain rewards and/or loyalty programs may be administered.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h4 id=&quot;information-we-collect&quot;&gt;2. Information We Collect.&lt;/h4&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;There are several areas on the Website and/or within the Application where you may be asked to enter both personal and non-personal information including, by way of example and without limitation, your name, address, phone number, credit card information, birthday, Facebook and/or Twitter usernames, and information regarding your cell phone and/or other mobile device. In addition, when you use the Application Pegke automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser or mobile platform, including your IP address and location. Pegke also collects and uses additional information from users such as transaction location, Application open date and time, idle time, and all clicks and/or swipes within the application (together with time and order). Pegke may also collect information posted by users on social media sites for users that have opted to connect to or otherwise link Pegke with social media accounts including Facebook and Twitter. We treat this data as non-personal information for purposes of providing the Services, except where we are required to treat it as personal information under applicable law. We DO NOT sell or share any personal information about you to or with any person or organization except
(i) as authorized by you,
(ii) as set forth in the relevant portion of the Website, Application or within any agreement between us,
(iii) in connection with providing various products or Services to you (either directly or through one or more third parties),
(iv) as may be required by law or court order, or
(vi) as otherwise set forth herein. In particular, and not in limitation of the foregoing, information you enter at the Website and/or Application (i) will be shared with the merchants or third party service providers with which Pegke has entered into a business relationship in order to provide the Services, and (ii) may be shared with various third parties in connection with making available to you certain offers (which offers may be based on or related to your location at the time the offer is made available to you). In addition, Pegke may sell, disclose or otherwise use information gathered on the Website or within the Application to third parties on an aggregated basis.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;(a) Information we receive from you. To use certain of Pegke’s Services and/or to access the Application, you’ll need to provide certain personal information which may include, without limitation, your name, address, birthday, phone number, credit card information, Facebook and/or Twitter user names, e-mail address, information regarding your cell phone or mobile device and other information.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;(b) Technical information we collect. In order for Pegke to ensure that we are providing the best possible consumer experience on the Website and within the Application, we collect and track certain user information. When you visit the Website, our Web server may send a cookie to your computer. This cookie would be intended to store a limited amount of information about your site visit. The cookie tracks aggregate information on how our site is being used, including session counts, navigation patterns, pages visited, etc. These cookies, however, do not store any personally identifiable information such as your name, email address or phone number as you browse the site. When you submit a question, we store your cookie identification in our system. This cookie allows our site to recognize you when you return. Pegke may also utilize Web Logs to track aggregate information about how our site and/or the Application is being used. Web Logs track anonymous user information, including the number of visitors to the Website, operating systems, Internet Provider addresses (if publicly available), and browser type. Unlike cookies, Web Logs are maintained only on Pegke servers and do not store or place anything on the user’s computer.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;If you come to the Pegke Website from an online banner ad, an anonymous identification number may be passed to the Website. This information cannot be used to gather any personally identifiable information about you. It will only allow us to track the overall effectiveness of our online advertising, marketing and banner advertisement campaigns.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;(c) Other Information we get from your use of the Services. We may collect information about the Services that you use and how you use them. This information includes:&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Device information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;We may collect device-specific information (such as your hardware model, operating system version, unique device identifiers, and mobile network information including phone number).&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;When you use the Service or access the Application, we may collect and process information about your actual location. We may also use various technologies to determine location, some of which may be made available through third party licensors.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;(d) Information from surveys. You may have the option of completing an online survey at the Website or within the Application from time to time. Participation in surveys is completely voluntary and it is your choice whether or not you wish to disclose your personal information to us in connection with any such survey.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;(e) Information from the “Contact Us” section of the Website or Application. You may contact Pegke through the “Contact Us” feature. Participation in this area is completely voluntary and it is your choice whether or not you wish to disclose your personal information to us.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;(f) Information collected other sections of the Website or Application. Pegke may, from time to time, make various resources available to you at the Website or within the Application. At times we may collect personal information in connection with providing such services.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h4 id=&quot;how-your-information-is-used&quot;&gt;3. How Your Information Is Used.&lt;/h4&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;We use the information you provide to provide the applicable Services to you, either directly or through third party service providers, as further described above in this Privacy Policy. Pegke may also share certain aggregated data with other third parties for general marketing and demographic purposes; however, this data, when shared on an aggregated basis, does not include any of your personal identifying information. Some of our Services may be offered in conjunction with partner companies, affiliates or other companies or websites with which we work. In order for us to provide these Services to you, it may be necessary for us to share your personal information with one of such entities. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these Services. If you do not want your data to be shared, you can choose not to allow the transfer by not using that particular Service.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;In addition, Pegke may disclose account or other personal information when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with Pegke’s rights or property, other Website or Application users or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h4 id=&quot;altering-information-you-submit&quot;&gt;4. Altering Information You Submit.&lt;/h4&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;(a) Deleting your information. Government regulations may require that we store questions or submissions for various periods of time. In order to comply with these regulations, we may be unable to delete information from our databases.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;(b) Altering Information. Pegke may alter, modify or delete any information you submit to the Website or through the Application if it believes, in its sole discretion, it is necessary or desirable to do so.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;(c) Request to stop receiving emails from us. Periodically, Pegke may send you emails to alert you to various opportunities or offers available at the Website or within the Application. If you do not wish to receive any of these offers, please send an e-mail to &lt;a href=&quot;support@pegke.com&quot;&gt;support@pegke.com&lt;/a&gt; to remove yourself from our mailing list.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h3 id=&quot;changes-to-privacy-policy&quot;&gt;Changes to Privacy Policy&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;If we make a change to our Privacy Policy in the future that will affect how we treat your information, we will post such change at the Website and/or within the Application, and such change will be deemed to be effective 2 days from the date of such posting. In that case, your ability to opt out of the new policy will be determined by applicable laws.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h3 id=&quot;business-transfer&quot;&gt;Business Transfer&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;We may, in the future, sell or otherwise transfer some or all of our assets or equity to a third party. Your personally identifiable information and other information we obtain from you via the Website or the Application may be disclosed to any potential or actual third party purchasers of such assets or equity and may be among the assets transferred.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h3 id=&quot;acceptance&quot;&gt;Acceptance&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not provide us with any information and do not use the Website or the Application. By using the Website or the Application and voluntarily providing information to us, you consent to our collection and use of the information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h4 id=&quot;links&quot;&gt;Links&lt;/h4&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;The Website and/or Application may contain links to other websites or applications that are owned and operated by third parties that are not affiliated with us. When you use those links, you leave the Website or Application (as applicable) and we are unable to control how the owners of the websites or applications you link to handle any information they gather about you, including their privacy practices and use of cookies. This Privacy Policy applies only to the Website and Application and does not govern activities on linked websites or applications. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of any other website or application you visit, download or access to understand its owner’s practices on how it collects, uses and discloses your information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>https://pegke.com/about/privacy-policy</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pegke.com/about/privacy-policy</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
