<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Customer Loyalty &amp;amp; Retention Management Software</title>
    <description>Customer Loyalty &amp;amp; Retention Management Software, integrates with merchant POS systems to give consumers a single identity to earn business-specific rewards</description>
    <link>https://pegke.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://pegke.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>2016-05-11T22:09:38+05:30</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>2016-05-11T22:09:38+05:30</lastBuildDate>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to start a loyalty rewards program for your customers</title>
        <description>Loyalty points are a must have to keep your customers loyal to your brand, it is more important when you’re small or medium business. Loyalty points, rewards program or loyalty discount is the best way to encourage customers to refer more clients to your business and thereby earn their loyalty.Pegke Loyalty is the easiest way to create a reward point system.How can I send the points?There are countless possibilities, all it matters is how you value the possibilities and how much points you can afford to give. We have various types of integra...</description>
        <pubDate>2016-05-02T00:00:00+05:30</pubDate>
        <link>https://pegke.com/blog/start-loyalty-rewards-program-your-customers</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pegke.com/blog/start-loyalty-rewards-program-your-customers</guid>
        
          <category>Loyalty</category>
        
          <category>rewards</category>
        
        
          <category>Marketing</category>
        
          <category>Rewards</category>
        
          <category>Loyalty Software</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Redeem Options</title>
        <description>Own ProductsYou can offer your ouwn products as redeemable items, all these options are managable from your dashboard.Gift VouchersYou can offer your customers many other gift vouchers of other companiesMobile RechargeYou can allow your customers to redeem your points as mobile recharge, of many pre-paid and post paid services.</description>
        <pubDate>2016-03-03T00:00:00+05:30</pubDate>
        <link>https://pegke.com/about/redeem-points</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pegke.com/about/redeem-points</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>On-demand Marketing and Customer Loyalty</title>
        <description>Digital media drove a shift in marketers’ budgets to “always-on” digital media, such as search, display, and social.  That focus is moving now to “always relevant” marketing. For brands and their agencies, this shift requires a much more sophisticated and targeted approach to address the ubiquity of touch points so that they can be there at a consumer’s moment of need—no matter where or when it is. In this environment, advertising needs to become a service.35% Online buyers willing to share personal information in return for targeted offers....</description>
        <pubDate>2016-01-30T00:00:00+05:30</pubDate>
        <link>https://pegke.com/blog/on-demand-marketing-customer-loyalty</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pegke.com/blog/on-demand-marketing-customer-loyalty</guid>
        
          <category>Marketing</category>
        
        
          <category>Marketing</category>
        
          <category>Tips</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Our Team</title>
        <description>Co-founder and Director of Enterprise Marketing.                                                                        Nikhil Mohan                  VP of Enterprise Marketing                                                                                                                                            Steve Jobes is a fictional character designed to resemble someone familiar to readers.                                                                        Sibiraj P.R.                  CTO                                        ...</description>
        <pubDate>2016-01-25T00:00:00+05:30</pubDate>
        <link>https://pegke.com/about/team</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pegke.com/about/team</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Anti-spam Legislation India</title>
        <description>The CAN-SPAM ActDo you use email in your business? The CAN-SPAM Act, a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have you stop emailing them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.Unsolicited Electronic Mail also called “spam” is a growing concern among corporations and individuals. Spamming, once viewed as a mere nuisance, is now posing some alarming problems. In the year 2002 alone, losses to US Corporations due to spamming were a staggering $8.9 bi...</description>
        <pubDate>2016-01-05T00:00:00+05:30</pubDate>
        <link>https://pegke.com/blog/can-spam-act-india</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pegke.com/blog/can-spam-act-india</guid>
        
          <category>terms</category>
        
        
          <category>CAN-SPAM</category>
        
          <category>Email</category>
        
          <category>Terms</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Pegke interacts with your POS</title>
        <description>What is Pegke Customer Loyalty ProgramPegke is an easy to use customer loyalty program or a reward point system, beneficial to both the business and the customer. Businesses drive attention of customers through customer loyalty programs by offering fantastic ways to reward and say thank you to their customers.The point of sale (POS) is the time and place where a retail transaction is completed. It is the point at which a customer makes a payment to the merchant in exchange for goods or after provision of a service.How Pegke Customer Loyalty ...</description>
        <pubDate>2016-01-03T00:00:00+05:30</pubDate>
        <link>https://pegke.com/blog/pegke-customer-loyalty-intgrate-pos-inventory</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pegke.com/blog/pegke-customer-loyalty-intgrate-pos-inventory</guid>
        
          <category>Loyalty Program</category>
        
        
          <category>Loyalty Program</category>
        
          <category>Pegke Loyalty Software</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Top 5 Customer Loyalty Trends of 2016</title>
        <description>In all actuality client experience does make a difference. Brands that can give fun, satisfying encounters through great deals stages and additional items like dedication projects have the capacity to catch more rehash clients, who pivot and get new clients they could call their own through image evangelism.  Omni-channel Engagement  Enthusiastic LOYALTY  Client examination takes focal point of the audience.  Personalization and accomplice showcasing  Experiential prizes = greatest effect.1. Omni-channel EngagementCustomer Loyalty Program ve...</description>
        <pubDate>2016-01-02T00:00:00+05:30</pubDate>
        <link>https://pegke.com/blog/top-5-customer-loyalty-trends-2016</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pegke.com/blog/top-5-customer-loyalty-trends-2016</guid>
        
          <category>trends</category>
        
        
          <category>Loyalty Program</category>
        
          <category>Loyalty Trends</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Loyalty over the Holidays</title>
        <description>Amid the extreme center of attention on scoring revenue in a sea of competitors, it can be easy to omit what must be the precedence — successful a patron who sticks round long after the ultimate slice of ham is eaten and the lights come down. If the value of loyalty escapes you, understand this: consistent with Harvard business review, growing patron retention rates by just 5% raises gains with the aid of 25% to 95%.1. Build personal connections with dataIn a be taught released in the Journal of applied Social Psychology, researchers learned...</description>
        <pubDate>2015-12-21T00:00:00+05:30</pubDate>
        <link>https://pegke.com/blog/customer-loyalty-over-holidays</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pegke.com/blog/customer-loyalty-over-holidays</guid>
        
        
          <category>Holidays</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Customer Retention Strategies</title>
        <description>The results of customer retention additionally compound after some time, and in at times unforeseen ways. Indeed, even a modest change in customer retention can course through a business framework and increase after some time. The subsequent impact on long haul benefit and development shouldn’t be thought little of.Pegke can acquaint you with various basic customer retention techniques that will cost you or nothing to actualize. Behind every system recorded here there is a top to bottom regulated procedure that will build your customer reten...</description>
        <pubDate>2015-12-21T00:00:00+05:30</pubDate>
        <link>https://pegke.com/blog/customer-retention-strategies</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pegke.com/blog/customer-retention-strategies</guid>
        
          <category>Retention</category>
        
        
          <category>Loyalty Program</category>
        
          <category>Retention</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Check your points</title>
        <description>Download our app from app store and earn poits from the installing itself,    keep the app ready for your next purchase.                      Not a Member Yet?                    Get the Mobile App        earn loyalty points                     Chose your platform                                                                                                              Select Country              Argentina  Australia  Bahrain  Belgium  Brazil  British Virgin Islands  Cameroon  Canada  Czech Republic  Denmark  Dominica  Egypt  England  Euro...</description>
        <pubDate>2015-12-20T00:00:00+05:30</pubDate>
        <link>https://pegke.com/check-points/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pegke.com/check-points/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Customer Loyalty Program Software for Restaurants</title>
        <description>Pegke is a customer loyalty programs for restaurants - as well, which utilizes the Smartphone and Tablet to manage the program; Pegke is the one solution that allows restaurants to create loyalty campaigns enabling them to attract more customers.Customer loyalty has been vital to restaurants of numerous types subsequent to the idea of an “restaurant” was made. Loyal customers are the ones who will return regularly and spend as often as possible, which helps restaurants of all sizes meet their main concerns. However building loyalty is not an...</description>
        <pubDate>2015-12-10T00:00:00+05:30</pubDate>
        <link>https://pegke.com/blog/customer-loyalty-program-software-for-restaurants</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pegke.com/blog/customer-loyalty-program-software-for-restaurants</guid>
        
          <category>Loyalty</category>
        
          <category>Restaurants</category>
        
        
          <category>Loyalty Program</category>
        
          <category>Restaurants</category>
        
          <category>Loyalty Software</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Technology stack</title>
        <description>Application and Data                                                                                                                                  Utilities                                                                          DevOps                                          Business Tools                                  We Love Developers      You&#39;ve came this far, we appreciate that... :)            Quick Links  GitHub  Support  Join Our Team  API  Developer FAQ</description>
        <pubDate>2015-12-10T00:00:00+05:30</pubDate>
        <link>https://pegke.com/about/technology-stack</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pegke.com/about/technology-stack</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Brand Guidelines</title>
        <description>Usage              The Pegke Loyalty marks include the Pegke Loyalty name and logo, and any word, phrase, image, or other designation that identifies the source or origin of any of Pegke Loyalty&#39;s products. Please don&#39;t modify the marks or use them in a confusing way, including suggesting sponsorship or endorsement by Pegke Loyalty, or in a way that confuses Pegke Loyalty with another brand (including your own).                                                    Download Logos          Our brand assets can be downloaded from Brandfolder.    ...</description>
        <pubDate>2015-12-10T00:00:00+05:30</pubDate>
        <link>https://pegke.com/about/brand-guidelines</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pegke.com/about/brand-guidelines</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pegke Status</title>
        <description>All Systems Operational #PegkeStat        Last updated on: ---                               Past Incidents          To know about past incidents please subscribe to #PegkeStat on Twitter            #PegkeStat Tweets</description>
        <pubDate>2015-11-25T00:00:00+05:30</pubDate>
        <link>https://pegke.com/about/system-status</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pegke.com/about/system-status</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Join Our Team</title>
        <description>A lot of companies talk about culture, their awesome office, fun events and great perks. But we view culture differently. We believe it&#39;s about rallying people who enjoy each other&#39;s company and respect each other&#39;s skill. It&#39;s about working alongside people you rely on to spar with you intellectually one moment, then grab tacos with you the next.                    We&#39;ve created a culture that rewards bright, driven, and fun-loving people. We take our work seriously. But ourselves? Not so much.            At Pegke Loyalty &amp;#8482; you can......</description>
        <pubDate>2015-11-25T00:00:00+05:30</pubDate>
        <link>https://pegke.com/about/careers</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pegke.com/about/careers</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Developer Docs</title>
        <description>Two-legged OAuth, or “signed fetch”, takes advantage of OAuth’s signatures to authenticate server-to-server requests. It doesn’t need to involve the user nor any access tokens.    If a consumer site wants to make an authorized API call to a provider site, they can simply sign the request the same way that they would sign a request token request. The provider verifies the signature and services the request if the consumer is authorized.    Two-legged OAuth is not well specified in any standards docs that I’ve seen. It’s more of a convenient r...</description>
        <pubDate>2015-11-22T00:00:00+05:30</pubDate>
        <link>https://pegke.com/api/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pegke.com/api/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Developer FAQ</title>
        <description>App token has expired!              First, that is a good thing. Tokens are like cash, if you have it you can use it. You don&#39;t need to prove that token belongs to you, so don&#39;t let anyone steal your token. In order to lower the risk tokens should expire fairly quickly. If your token expires in 120s then it will be only usable during that window.                    What do I do if my token was expired?                      Along with your access token, an authentication token is created. It&#39;s called the refresh token . It&#39;s a longer lived to...</description>
        <pubDate>2015-11-22T00:00:00+05:30</pubDate>
        <link>https://pegke.com/api/faq</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pegke.com/api/faq</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Customer Loyalty Program</title>
        <description>Why a Customer Loyalty Program ?Customers finding it difficult to stay loyal to your business? Tired of following a single brand that does not reward you for your loyalty? Enter the Pegke Customer Loyalty &amp;amp; Rewards Software that not only rewards the customers for their brand loyalty but also makes the customers stay loyal to their favorite franchises. Pegke is not just another app in the store, it is an easy-to-use software designed and shaped elegantly by Technopark engineers that is advantageous to both the business and customers. The ...</description>
        <pubDate>2015-11-19T00:00:00+05:30</pubDate>
        <link>https://pegke.com/customer-loyalty-program</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pegke.com/customer-loyalty-program</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What is Pegke?</title>
        <description>Pegke is a Customer Loyalty &amp;amp; Retention Management Software, which integrates with merchant POS systems to give consumers a single identity to earn business-specific rewards.  Pegke is a Customer Loyalty &amp;amp; Retention Management Software, which integrates with merchant POS systems to give consumers a single identity to earn business-specific rewards.Best way to juggle money on things you love or on places you most often visit.  Pegke is an easy to use customer loyalty program or a reward point system, beneficial to both the merchant an...</description>
        <pubDate>2015-11-17T00:00:00+05:30</pubDate>
        <link>https://pegke.com/faq/what-is-pegke</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pegke.com/faq/what-is-pegke</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Retail Sector</title>
        <description>We believe that business objectives and users’ goals should be treated as equals, and that doing this creates winning brand experiences.  Our opinion is that insight and understanding are crucial for achieving success but also know that, on occasions, unnecessarily bloated research projects can delay progress. To this end we have made a conscious effort to be able to provide insight for businesses of any size in an agile timeframe.  How we can help you  If you can’t confidently answer yes to all of the following questions, you would benefit ...</description>
        <pubDate>2015-11-16T00:00:00+05:30</pubDate>
        <link>https://pegke.com/business/retail-sector</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pegke.com/business/retail-sector</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
