<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
   
   	<title>RealJenius.com - Tag: Restaurants</title>
   
   <link>http://realjenius.com</link>
   <description>I'm a software developer in the game industry, and have been (for better or worse) coding on the Java platform for the last decade. I also do all my own stunts.</description>
   <language>en-us</language>
   <managingEditor>R.J. Lorimer</managingEditor>
   <atom:link href="rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

    
	  <item>
        <title>Customer Loyalty Program Software for Restaurants</title>
        <link>http://realjenius.com/blog/customer-loyalty-program-software-for-restaurants</link>
		<author>R.J. Lorimer</author>
		<pubDate>2015-12-10T00:00:00+05:30</pubDate>
		<guid>http://realjenius.com/blog/customer-loyalty-program-software-for-restaurants</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[
		   <p>Pegke is a customer loyalty programs for restaurants - as well, which utilizes the Smartphone and Tablet to manage the program; Pegke is the one solution that allows restaurants to create loyalty campaigns enabling them to attract more customers.</p>

<p>Customer loyalty has been vital to restaurants of numerous types subsequent to the idea of an “restaurant” was made. Loyal customers are the ones who will return regularly and spend as often as possible, which helps restaurants of all sizes meet their main concerns. However building loyalty is not another idea for eatery proprietors, the strategies used to approach building customer loyalty have changed throughout the years.</p>

<div class="ui highlight">Loyal customers are the ones who will return regularly and spend as often as possible, which helps restaurants of all sizes meet their main concerns.</div>

<h2 id="traditionally-customer-loyalty-has-been-managed-by-one-of-the-following-methods">Traditionally Customer loyalty has been managed by one of the following methods.</h2>

<h4 id="punch-cards"><strong>Punch cards</strong></h4>

<p>Punch cards are one among the earliest kinds of loyalty building techniques. although the inducement of “buy 10 meals and obtain the 11th free” still appeals to some diners, it solely permits restaurant owners to reward customers for one action out of the many that they take.</p>

<h4 id="general-on-bill-discounts">General on-bill discounts</h4>

<p>Offering a discount to all customers might seem like a generous move by the restaurant, but is it really helping your brand build lasting loyalty? Unfortunately, research shows otherwise.</p>

<p>The fact of the matter is that frequent customers already like your restaurant, and although a couple bucks off on a menu item is always nice, it’s not why they keep coming back.</p>

<h2 id="is-this-for-the-future">Is this for the future?</h2>

<p><strong>Of course its not</strong>, thats why we made a <strong>Customer Loyalty &amp; Retention Management Platform</strong> which utilizes the Smartphone and Tablet to manage the program; Pegke is the one solution that allows restaurants to create loyalty campaigns enabling them to attract more customer flow to the restaurant.</p>

<h3 id="advantages-of-using-pegke-customer-loyalty-program-for-a-restaurant"><strong>Advantages of using Pegke Customer Loyalty Program for a Restaurant</strong></h3>

<h4 id="specialized-store-front"><strong>Specialized store front</strong></h4>

<p>A very robust and customizable store front for your online store. You can make this place to promote your latest offers and Nuggets you publish via the vendor dashboard.</p>

<h4 id="store-settings"><strong>Store Settings</strong></h4>

<p>You can customize the check-in interval for your customers on your shop. Its a few clicks away. Also you can switch from price range store or check-in store anytime based on your Subscription level</p>

<h4 id="demographics"><strong>Demographics</strong></h4>

<p>This is one of the best part of Pegke, you can view detailed graphs of your stores performance in real time, which will help you restructure your offers and Nuggets , if necessary.</p>

<h4 id="send-push-messages"><strong>Send Push Messages</strong></h4>

<p>Send Push messages to the customers. One of the impressive ways to enlighten customers, pickup sales and customer satisfaction.</p>

<p>Thats not all, read the complete list of Pegke <a href="https://pegke.com/vendor-app-features">Customer Loyalty Program Features</a></p>

		]]></description>
	  </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
