<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
   
    <title>RealJenius.com - Category: Restaurants</title>
   
   <link>http://realjenius.com</link>
   <description>I'm a software developer in the game industry, and have been (for better or worse) coding on the Java platform for the last decade. I also do all my own stunts.</description>
   <language>en-us</language>
   <managingEditor>R.J. Lorimer</managingEditor>
   <atom:link href="rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

    
	  <item>
        <title>Customer Loyalty Program Software for Restaurants</title>
        <link>http://realjenius.com/blog/customer-loyalty-program-software-for-restaurants</link>
		<author>R.J. Lorimer</author>
		<pubDate>2015-12-10T00:00:00+05:30</pubDate>
		<guid>http://realjenius.com/blog/customer-loyalty-program-software-for-restaurants</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[
		   <p>Pegke is a customer loyalty programs for restaurants - as well, which utilizes the Smartphone and Tablet to manage the program; Pegke is the one solution that allows restaurants to create loyalty campaigns enabling them to attract more customers.</p>

<p>Customer loyalty has been vital to restaurants of numerous types subsequent to the idea of an “restaurant” was made. Loyal customers are the ones who will return regularly and spend as often as possible, which helps restaurants of all sizes meet their main concerns. However building loyalty is not another idea for eatery proprietors, the strategies used to approach building customer loyalty have changed throughout the years.</p>

<div class="ui highlight">Loyal customers are the ones who will return regularly and spend as often as possible, which helps restaurants of all sizes meet their main concerns.</div>

<h2 id="traditionally-customer-loyalty-has-been-managed-by-one-of-the-following-methods">Traditionally Customer loyalty has been managed by one of the following methods.</h2>

<h4 id="punch-cards"><strong>Punch cards</strong></h4>

<p>Punch cards are one among the earliest kinds of loyalty building techniques. although the inducement of “buy 10 meals and obtain the 11th free” still appeals to some diners, it solely permits restaurant owners to reward customers for one action out of the many that they take.</p>

<h4 id="general-on-bill-discounts">General on-bill discounts</h4>

<p>Offering a discount to all customers might seem like a generous move by the restaurant, but is it really helping your brand build lasting loyalty? Unfortunately, research shows otherwise.</p>

<p>The fact of the matter is that frequent customers already like your restaurant, and although a couple bucks off on a menu item is always nice, it’s not why they keep coming back.</p>

<h2 id="is-this-for-the-future">Is this for the future?</h2>

<p><strong>Of course its not</strong>, thats why we made a <strong>Customer Loyalty &amp; Retention Management Platform</strong> which utilizes the Smartphone and Tablet to manage the program; Pegke is the one solution that allows restaurants to create loyalty campaigns enabling them to attract more customer flow to the restaurant.</p>

<h3 id="advantages-of-using-pegke-customer-loyalty-program-for-a-restaurant"><strong>Advantages of using Pegke Customer Loyalty Program for a Restaurant</strong></h3>

<h4 id="specialized-store-front"><strong>Specialized store front</strong></h4>

<p>A very robust and customizable store front for your online store. You can make this place to promote your latest offers and Nuggets you publish via the vendor dashboard.</p>

<h4 id="store-settings"><strong>Store Settings</strong></h4>

<p>You can customize the check-in interval for your customers on your shop. Its a few clicks away. Also you can switch from price range store or check-in store anytime based on your Subscription level</p>

<h4 id="demographics"><strong>Demographics</strong></h4>

<p>This is one of the best part of Pegke, you can view detailed graphs of your stores performance in real time, which will help you restructure your offers and Nuggets , if necessary.</p>

<h4 id="send-push-messages"><strong>Send Push Messages</strong></h4>

<p>Send Push messages to the customers. One of the impressive ways to enlighten customers, pickup sales and customer satisfaction.</p>

<p>Thats not all, read the complete list of Pegke <a href="https://pegke.com/vendor-app-features">Customer Loyalty Program Features</a></p>

		]]></description>
	  </item>
    
	  <item>
        <title>A Checklist to Get Your Customer Loyalty Program off the Ground</title>
        <link>http://realjenius.com/blog/checklist-get-your-customer-loyalty-program-ground</link>
		<author>R.J. Lorimer</author>
		<pubDate>2015-11-12T00:00:00+05:30</pubDate>
		<guid>http://realjenius.com/blog/checklist-get-your-customer-loyalty-program-ground</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[
		   <p>Customer Loyalty ought to be a go-to methodology for any small business, yet the fact of the matter is, paying little heed to if the system is computerized or an old-school punch card, little entrepreneurs don’t feel like they have room schedule-wise to tackle more obligation.</p>

<p>In any case, dispatching a client reliability project doesn’t need to take a town. What’s more, what is the most exceedingly terrible thing that can happen in the event that you take a couple of additional minutes to actualize one? You compensate your current clients, expand deals and possibly pick up a couple of new ones? Sounds like a win-win circumstance.</p>

<h3 id="agenda-for-making-your-own-particular-computerized-customer-loyalty-program">Agenda for making your own particular computerized Customer Loyalty program.</h3>

<h4 id="clear-objectives">1. Clear objectives</h4>

<p>Is there a particular target bunch - taking into account spending limits, buys recurrence or other particular division - or is everyone qualified? What would you like to accomplish for the target bunch with the client devotion program? How would you characterize achievement and by what means will you measure it? How is your project adjusted to the general showcasing method?</p>

<ul>
  <li>Your objectives could be to</li>
  <li>Pull in new clients</li>
  <li>Hold existing clients</li>
  <li>Win more noteworthy offer of wallet</li>
  <li>Brief clients to make extra buys</li>
  <li>Invigorate clients to purchase different items or administrations</li>
  <li>Turn a benefit for the project itself</li>
</ul>

<h4 id="begin-considering-the-end">2. Begin considering the end.</h4>

<p>Before you lose trace of what’s most important, make a stride back and choose what you need to escape from your client steadfastness program. Enhance client securing? Diminish client agitate? Expansion request size? Make these objectives as particular and as quantifiable as could be allowed.</p>

<h4 id="brilliant-mechanization">3. Brilliant mechanization</h4>

<p>In what capacity would you be able to mechanize the distinctive procedure ventures in your dependability program? In what capacity would you be able to adjust simplicity of administration/upkeep with personalization? What kind of incorporations are essential?</p>

<p>A few things to look at</p>

<ul>
  <li>By what means will we urge clients to sign up and what choices do we give?</li>
  <li>Do we require IT joining with POS, CRM or different frameworks? Is it one-way or two-way?</li>
  <li>What client division information will we gather?</li>
  <li>What significant client experiences do we get from the reporting?</li>
</ul>

<h4 id="platform-stability">4. Platform Stability</h4>

<p>Is the SaaS arrangement versatile, performant and sufficiently secure for your needs? Does it cover all your current useful needs out-of-the-container? Does your supplier sufficiently offer assurances sponsored by an administration level assertion?</p>

<p>A few things to look at</p>

<ul>
  <li>SLA on front-end cloud application administration accessibility</li>
  <li>SLA on client administration reaction time</li>
  <li>Expansiveness and profundity of practical offer</li>
  <li>Experience specialized reconciliationExisting reporting abilities</li>
  <li>Readiness to give client particular highlights and augmentations</li>
  <li>Quality affirmation over the worth chain (from client sign up to request satisfaction)</li>
  <li>Test correspondences with a sounding gathering</li>
</ul>

<h4 id="significant-prizes">5. Significant prizes</h4>

<p>What will make your workers feel generally refreshing? (Incidentally, there is a significant improvement with ‘What do your workers need?’) Do the prizes mirror your way of life and targets? Does the supplier show adaptability (e.g. to incorporate your own particular items)?</p>

<p>A few things to look at</p>

<ul>
  <li>Does it incorporate blend of stock, encounters and philanthropy?</li>
  <li>Does the quantity of honor things upgrades or reduces the acknowledgment experience?</li>
  <li>Do the honor things speak to client “needs” and not simply “needs” to give a sense or extravagance or spoiling?</li>
  <li>Will it emerge from what contenders are doing?</li>
</ul>

<h4 id="reach-out-and-touch-a-client---with-email">6. Reach out and touch a client - with email.</h4>

<p>Staying in touch through email is one of the least demanding and best approaches to commence an advanced devotion battle. Begin straightforward by making a constant flow of correspondence around your dependability program.</p>

<h4 id="go-social">7. Go social.</h4>

<p>Online networking is an amazingly successful approach to draw in with existing clients all the time. Take the time to comprehend which online networking channels - Facebook, Pinterest, Foursquare and Instagram to give some examples - your clients draw in with the most. Once you’ve chosen the privilege network(s), assemble your social group through fluctuated and drawing in substance and posts – making numerous alternatives for imparting.</p>

		]]></description>
	  </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
