<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
   
    <title>RealJenius.com - Category: Loyalty Points</title>
   
   <link>http://realjenius.com</link>
   <description>I'm a software developer in the game industry, and have been (for better or worse) coding on the Java platform for the last decade. I also do all my own stunts.</description>
   <language>en-us</language>
   <managingEditor>R.J. Lorimer</managingEditor>
   <atom:link href="rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

    
	  <item>
        <title>How to start a loyalty rewards program for your customers</title>
        <link>http://realjenius.com/blog/start-loyalty-rewards-program-your-customers</link>
		<author>R.J. Lorimer</author>
		<pubDate>2016-05-02T00:00:00+05:30</pubDate>
		<guid>http://realjenius.com/blog/start-loyalty-rewards-program-your-customers</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[
		   <p>Loyalty points are a must have to keep your customers loyal to your brand, it is more important when you’re small or medium business. Loyalty points, rewards program or loyalty discount is the best way to encourage customers to refer more clients to your business and thereby earn their loyalty.</p>

<div class="ui highlight">Pegke Loyalty is the easiest way to create a reward point system.</div>

<h2 id="how-can-i-send-the-points">How can I send the points?</h2>
<p>There are countless possibilities, all it matters is how you value the possibilities and how much points you can afford to give. We have various types of integration, specifically;</p>

<ol>
  <li>Printed Points</li>
  <li>Web dashboard</li>
  <li>API integration.</li>
</ol>

<h3 id="1-sign-up-to-pegke-loyalty">1. Sign up to Pegke Loyalty</h3>
<p>You can sign up to <a href="#signup" class="ctal">Pegke Loyalty</a> giving your phone number, email and physical address of your business.</p>

<div class="ui highlight">You will get  ₹1000.00 to start with all the features included.</div>

<h3 id="2-create-redeemable-items">2. Create redeemable Items.</h3>
<p>Redeemable items are something that your customer can redeem when he have enough points. You can define the number of points required to redeem this particular item. You can add an image, also you can specify a time period where this item is available for redemption.</p>

<p class="ui image fluid lazy"><img src="https://pegke.com/public/blogs/add-redeemable-item.png" alt="redeemable items" /></p>

<h3 id="3-give-points">3. Give points</h3>
<p>Yes, you can give points from now on, all you need is your customers phone number.</p>

<p class="ui image fluid lazy"><img src="https://pegke.com/public/blogs/send-points.png" alt="Give Loyalty points" /></p>

<h3 id="4-track-analyze-improve">4. Track, Analyze, Improve</h3>

<p class="ui image fluid lazy">You can see the complete activity in Pegke Dashboard and you can plan for your next big offer according to the data insights captured and tailored for you.
<img src="https://pegke.com/public/blogs/pegke-dashboard.png" alt="Pegke Dashboard" /></p>

<p class="ui image fluid lazy"><img src="https://pegke.com/public/blogs/earned-points.png" alt="Earned Points" /></p>

<h3 id="5-whats-next">5. Whats next?</h3>

<p>You can run loyalty campaigns to attract more customers and increase sales. Stay put for the next update.</p>

		]]></description>
	  </item>
    
	  <item>
        <title>Loyalty over the Holidays</title>
        <link>http://realjenius.com/blog/customer-loyalty-over-holidays</link>
		<author>R.J. Lorimer</author>
		<pubDate>2015-12-21T00:00:00+05:30</pubDate>
		<guid>http://realjenius.com/blog/customer-loyalty-over-holidays</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[
		   <p>Amid the extreme center of attention on scoring revenue in a sea of competitors, it can be easy to omit what must be the precedence — successful a patron who sticks round long after the ultimate slice of ham is eaten and the lights come down. If the value of loyalty escapes you, understand this: consistent with Harvard business review, growing patron retention rates by just 5% raises gains with the aid of 25% to 95%.</p>

<h2 id="1-build-personal-connections-with-data">1. Build personal connections with data</h2>

<p>In a be taught released in the Journal of applied Social Psychology, researchers learned that waiters were competent to broaden their suggestions by 23% quite simply by offering their purchasers a 2nd set of mints and framing the act as if it had been for them and them best.</p>

<p>The lesson to study right here is that a private, significant connection is predominant to getting probably the most out of persons, and how to attain that is through purchaser information.</p>

<p>Even some thing as simple as collecting data on whether or not a bought item is a gift can be utilized to ship a pleasant follow-up that offers the buyer something particular for himself or herself at the side of a question about how the present was once obtained.</p>

<h2 id="2-make-the-small-print-a-big-deal">2. Make the small print a big deal</h2>
<p>That is notably actual for the ever-trendy reward voucher buy, where traditionally phrases and conditions are murkier territory. Being entirely obvious can ruin down what in any other case perhaps a barrier to buy and ensure the buyer and recipient’s experiences are incredibly confident.</p>

<h2 id="3-bring-real-life-online-and-vice-versa">3. Bring real life, online and vice versa</h2>
<p>If you are still occupied with your small business internet site, social media platforms, web publication and actual lifestyles presence as separate entities with separate strategies: discontinue. The satisfactory advertising systems reside throughout your brand’s whole presence, creating one cohesive message that shows the world what you stand for.</p>

<p>Starbucks does this totally good with each and every celebration. This 12 months’s weird pink cup controversy is a testimony to how iconic the seasonal design tweak really is, and the company seamlessly integrates this in-retailer activation on-line with an Instagram pink Cup Contest which furnished content for Pinterest, facebook, and Twitter and a design tweak to deliver the festivities to the industry website. Regardless of a undoubtedly-large marketing price range, Starbucks still heralds easy recommendations and consistency throughout platforms - and strikes success every time.</p>

		]]></description>
	  </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
