<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
   
    <title>RealJenius.com - Category: Marketing</title>
   
   <link>http://realjenius.com</link>
   <description>I'm a software developer in the game industry, and have been (for better or worse) coding on the Java platform for the last decade. I also do all my own stunts.</description>
   <language>en-us</language>
   <managingEditor>R.J. Lorimer</managingEditor>
   <atom:link href="rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

    
	  <item>
        <title>How to start a loyalty rewards program for your customers</title>
        <link>http://realjenius.com/blog/start-loyalty-rewards-program-your-customers</link>
		<author>R.J. Lorimer</author>
		<pubDate>2016-05-02T00:00:00+05:30</pubDate>
		<guid>http://realjenius.com/blog/start-loyalty-rewards-program-your-customers</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[
		   <p>Loyalty points are a must have to keep your customers loyal to your brand, it is more important when you’re small or medium business. Loyalty points, rewards program or loyalty discount is the best way to encourage customers to refer more clients to your business and thereby earn their loyalty.</p>

<div class="ui highlight">Pegke Loyalty is the easiest way to create a reward point system.</div>

<h2 id="how-can-i-send-the-points">How can I send the points?</h2>
<p>There are countless possibilities, all it matters is how you value the possibilities and how much points you can afford to give. We have various types of integration, specifically;</p>

<ol>
  <li>Printed Points</li>
  <li>Web dashboard</li>
  <li>API integration.</li>
</ol>

<h3 id="sign-up-to-pegke-loyalty">1. Sign up to Pegke Loyalty</h3>
<p>You can sign up to <a href="#signup" class="ctal">Pegke Loyalty</a> giving your phone number, email and physical address of your business.</p>

<div class="ui highlight">You will get  ₹1000.00 to start with all the features included.</div>

<h3 id="create-redeemable-items">2. Create redeemable Items.</h3>
<p>Redeemable items are something that your customer can redeem when he have enough points. You can define the number of points required to redeem this particular item. You can add an image, also you can specify a time period where this item is available for redemption.</p>

<p class="ui image fluid lazy"><img src="https://pegke.com/public/blogs/add-redeemable-item.png" alt="redeemable items" /></p>

<h3 id="give-points">3. Give points</h3>
<p>Yes, you can give points from now on, all you need is your customers phone number.</p>

<p class="ui image fluid lazy"><img src="https://pegke.com/public/blogs/send-points.png" alt="Give Loyalty points" /></p>

<h3 id="track-analyze-improve">4. Track, Analyze, Improve</h3>

<p class="ui image fluid lazy">You can see the complete activity in Pegke Dashboard and you can plan for your next big offer according to the data insights captured and tailored for you.
<img src="https://pegke.com/public/blogs/pegke-dashboard.png" alt="Pegke Dashboard" /></p>

<p class="ui image fluid lazy"><img src="https://pegke.com/public/blogs/earned-points.png" alt="Earned Points" /></p>

<h3 id="whats-next">5. Whats next?</h3>

<p>You can run loyalty campaigns to attract more customers and increase sales. Stay put for the next update.</p>

		]]></description>
	  </item>
    
	  <item>
        <title>On-demand Marketing and Customer Loyalty</title>
        <link>http://realjenius.com/blog/on-demand-marketing-customer-loyalty</link>
		<author>R.J. Lorimer</author>
		<pubDate>2016-01-30T00:00:00+05:30</pubDate>
		<guid>http://realjenius.com/blog/on-demand-marketing-customer-loyalty</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[
		   <p>Digital media drove a shift in marketers’ budgets to “always-on” digital media, such as search, display, and social.  That focus is moving now to “always relevant” marketing. For brands and their agencies, this shift requires a much more sophisticated and targeted approach to address the ubiquity of touch points so that they can be there at a consumer’s moment of need—no matter where or when it is. In this environment, advertising needs to become a service.</p>

<div class="ui highlight">35% Online buyers willing to share personal information in return for targeted offers.</div>

<h2 id="on-demand-marketing">On-demand Marketing</h2>
<p>On-demand Marketing is usually explained as market only travellers have the a need or even public discussion on the service or product you’re selling. Superior analytics are assisting companies sense communications and respond with real-time with written content tailored to just about every customer “touch. ” NFC potato chips in phones, together with smart tags which could go on virtually any object, are opening up an “Internet of things” that is certainly intelligent, interactive, and also always accessible. Breakthroughs in cell technology are creating thousands of ways to touch base with consumers. As these opportunities to touch base with the client multiply, brands will need to have clear strategies to meet three primary customer demands: anywhere/anytime accessibility, personally relevant, and simple to use.</p>

<h3 id="customers-are-more-impatient-than-ever">Customers are more impatient than ever.</h3>

<p>They will wield mobile tech like smartphone samurai and also have increasingly high expectations on the brands they visit—be the idea online, on the phone or directly. Call it the Veruca Salt Doctrine—I want to buy, and I want the idea now. It’s a reality that’s driving the modern era of on-demand advertising and marketing.</p>

<p>Personalization can deliver several to eight times the ROI on marketing expend and lift sales 10% or even more.</p>

<div class="ui highlight">67% Customer decisions based on experiences with brands and categories, rather than price.</div>

<p>To win over on-demand customers, brands must know them, what they assume, and what works with him or her, and then have the chance to reach them with the right kind of interaction. Data lies in the middle of these efforts. To build the necessary level connected with understanding, companies need several distinct data lenses.</p>

<p>A particular view of the vast and long-term trends on the market, category, and brand is vital. Digital sources that track what people are trying to find (search), what people say (social monitoring), and what folks are doing (tracking online, mobile, and in-store activities) signify rivers of input providing constant warning signs of trouble or indicators of latent opportunity. Many companies are drowning in reports from vendors providing most of these information tools, yet few have a lot clarity on which things they have to look for and who must know what.</p>

<h4 id="loyalty-by-industry-sector">Loyalty by Industry Sector</h4>
<p class="ui image fluid lazy"><img src="https://pegke.com/public/img/loyalty-industry-sector.png" alt="On-demand Marketing Loyalty by Industry Sector " /></p>

<div class="ui header medium source">Sources</div>

<ul>
  <li>http://www.mckinseyonmarketingandsales.com/the-coming-era-of-on-demand-marketing</li>
  <li>http://www.economistinsights.com/marketing-consumer/opinion/demands-demand-marketing</li>
</ul>

		]]></description>
	  </item>
    
	  <item>
        <title>The History of the Marketing Concept</title>
        <link>http://realjenius.com/blog/history-marketing-concept</link>
		<author>R.J. Lorimer</author>
		<pubDate>2015-09-12T00:00:00+05:30</pubDate>
		<guid>http://realjenius.com/blog/history-marketing-concept</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[
		   <p>Aspects of modern marketing could be found in the practices of early traders and the bazaars of the Middle East…. traders in pre-Hellenic Greece displayed admirable customer focus, and the medieval book trade espoused a range of marketing strategies including selective distribution, celebrity endorsement, sponsorship and test marketing. Marketing functions were manifest in early joint-stock companies such as the East India Company and the Hudson’s Bay Company. While historians, by and large, will view the formation of the East India Company as a British prelude to the eventual conquest of the Indian subcontinent, a modern marketing strategist could view the East India Company, a tad charitably perhaps, as a British tactic to enter new markets with the ultimate aim of becoming the undisputed market leader in Southeast Asia. Such a view has parallels in the last century, and the best example is the invasion and eventual domination of the U.S. consumer electronic market by the Japanese via a seemingly innocuous presence in Europe.</p>

<p>The point is that marketing is an ancient practice, and the intellectual study of marketing is also several centuries old. The distinctive contribution of the 20th Century was the introduction of the specialist marketer. Whether the earliest was Procter and Gamble’s first brand manager for Camay soap in 1926 is an open question; other brands were professionally managed before then. It was only in the last 100 years that businesses and academics have had to train specialist marketers. Accordingly, the trainers needed better to understand the nature and theory of marketing.</p>

<p>One marketing standard chronology (Bartels, 1974; Dawson, 1969; Keith, 1960; Kotler and Keller, 2006) subdivides marketing history as follows:</p>

<ul>
  <li>Production orientation era</li>
  <li>Product orientation era</li>
  <li>Sales orientation era</li>
  <li>Market orientation era</li>
  <li>Customer orientation</li>
  <li>Relationship orientation</li>
  <li>Social/mobile marketing orientation</li>
</ul>

<p>Thus, we have entered the new millennium wherein marketing expertise &amp; innovation is the key to surviving, let alone flourishing, in the more competitive, constantly changing &amp; ever-expanding global economy…</p>

		]]></description>
	  </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
