<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
   
    <title>RealJenius.com - Category: Trends</title>
   
   <link>http://realjenius.com</link>
   <description>I'm a software developer in the game industry, and have been (for better or worse) coding on the Java platform for the last decade. I also do all my own stunts.</description>
   <language>en-us</language>
   <managingEditor>R.J. Lorimer</managingEditor>
   <atom:link href="rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

    
	  <item>
        <title>Loyalty over the Holidays</title>
        <link>http://realjenius.com/blog/customer-loyalty-over-holidays</link>
		<author>R.J. Lorimer</author>
		<pubDate>2015-12-21T00:00:00+05:30</pubDate>
		<guid>http://realjenius.com/blog/customer-loyalty-over-holidays</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[
		   <p>Amid the extreme center of attention on scoring revenue in a sea of competitors, it can be easy to omit what must be the precedence — successful a patron who sticks round long after the ultimate slice of ham is eaten and the lights come down. If the value of loyalty escapes you, understand this: consistent with Harvard business review, growing patron retention rates by just 5% raises gains with the aid of 25% to 95%.</p>

<h2 id="build-personal-connections-with-data">1. Build personal connections with data</h2>

<p>In a be taught released in the Journal of applied Social Psychology, researchers learned that waiters were competent to broaden their suggestions by 23% quite simply by offering their purchasers a 2nd set of mints and framing the act as if it had been for them and them best.</p>

<p>The lesson to study right here is that a private, significant connection is predominant to getting probably the most out of persons, and how to attain that is through purchaser information.</p>

<p>Even some thing as simple as collecting data on whether or not a bought item is a gift can be utilized to ship a pleasant follow-up that offers the buyer something particular for himself or herself at the side of a question about how the present was once obtained.</p>

<h2 id="make-the-small-print-a-big-deal">2. Make the small print a big deal</h2>
<p>That is notably actual for the ever-trendy reward voucher buy, where traditionally phrases and conditions are murkier territory. Being entirely obvious can ruin down what in any other case perhaps a barrier to buy and ensure the buyer and recipient’s experiences are incredibly confident.</p>

<h2 id="bring-real-life-online-and-vice-versa">3. Bring real life, online and vice versa</h2>
<p>If you are still occupied with your small business internet site, social media platforms, web publication and actual lifestyles presence as separate entities with separate strategies: discontinue. The satisfactory advertising systems reside throughout your brand’s whole presence, creating one cohesive message that shows the world what you stand for.</p>

<p>Starbucks does this totally good with each and every celebration. This 12 months’s weird pink cup controversy is a testimony to how iconic the seasonal design tweak really is, and the company seamlessly integrates this in-retailer activation on-line with an Instagram pink Cup Contest which furnished content for Pinterest, facebook, and Twitter and a design tweak to deliver the festivities to the industry website. Regardless of a undoubtedly-large marketing price range, Starbucks still heralds easy recommendations and consistency throughout platforms - and strikes success every time.</p>

		]]></description>
	  </item>
    
	  <item>
        <title>6 Customer Loyalty trends around the World</title>
        <link>http://realjenius.com/blog/customer-loyalty-whats-happening-around-world</link>
		<author>R.J. Lorimer</author>
		<pubDate>2015-11-10T00:00:00+05:30</pubDate>
		<guid>http://realjenius.com/blog/customer-loyalty-whats-happening-around-world</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[
		   <p>Reward programs are intended to exactly deliver this – be able to track and reward customer behavior. Statistics also indicate that consumer participation in rewards programs is on the rise across all demographic segments. With more customers choosing to do coupon and bargain shopping in the store, the reward programs that provide personalized rewards will prove to be differentiators if implemented with a laser sharp focus on targeted customer segments.</p>

<p>Best-Practices to take customer loyalty program to the next level.</p>

<ul>
  <li>Segment Based Personalization</li>
  <li>“Value”Driven</li>
  <li>“Personalize” Rewards</li>
  <li>Reward “In-store”</li>
  <li>Cross-Channel “Common” Messaging</li>
  <li>Break Boundaries for acquiring Customers</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="segment-based-personalization">1. Segment Based Personalization</h3>

<p>The way to winning the devotion diversion is to have the capacity to rightly fragment clients, and make offers in light of the sections’ profiles. Retailers are doing this in numerous ways – selecting clients in distinctive levels with clients getting the opportunity to sign-up on less premium levels and retailers having control on moving up to the high premium levels (with better advantages). The division is ordinarily based on present/saw ROI and/or the client’s propensity.</p>

<h3 id="valuedriven">2. “Value”Driven</h3>

<p>Today’s customer loyalty program can’t stand to remain a ‘rebate card’ and need to broaden past plain rewards. Retailers are moving from focuses and rebates to customized administrations, exchanging prizes to philanthropy projects, green activities, night-time shopping, access to item manuals, formulas, articles, “how to”guides and bulletins.</p>

<h3 id="personalize-rewards">3. “Personalize” Rewards</h3>

<p>Certain retailers make “clubs”that mirror clients’ enthusiasm for particular classes and permit the clients to infer unmistakable and elusive advantages by being individuals from these clubs. Some cases of clubs advanced by retailers are “Child Clubs”,”Home Décor Clubs”, “Natural Foods Club” and so on . This is another path for the clients to inform retailers concerning their extraordinary enthusiasm for certain classes</p>

<h3 id="reward-in-store">4. Reward “In-store”</h3>

<p>Moment satisfaction at the Point of Sale or In-store as far as offers on items, moment coupons for next buy, occasion based dialogs/messages (e.g. extraordinary occasions like birthdays or dropping a thing in the internet shopping basket), thankfulness for a high total assets client are a percentage of the opportunity zones for retailers.</p>

<p>Retailers gather data about clients and their shopping propensities and utilization it to manufacture an exact picture of customer interest, plan exact advancements in light of information investigation and convey it in-store. POS is advancing as a complex instrument equipped for managing this gigantic measure of client and business insight.</p>

<h3 id="cross-channel-common-messaging">5. Cross-Channel “Common” Messaging</h3>

<p>Huge retailers working various organizations and connecting at numerous client touch-focuses are concentrating on incorporating the faithfulness project to guarantee that the client has admittance to the same offerings over the channels.</p>

<h3 id="break-boundaries-for-acquiring-customers">6. Break Boundaries for acquiring Customers</h3>

<p>Retailers are additionally utilizing faithfulness projects to spur multi-channel connection, for instance if a purchaser normally buys in store, a coupon can be offered as a motivating force to buy on the web.Huge retailers working various organizations and connecting at numerous client touch-focuses are concentrating on incorporating the faithfulness project to guarantee that the client has admittance to the same offerings over the channels.</p>

<p>Retailers are additionally utilizing faithfulness projects to spur multi-channel connection, for instance if a purchaser normally buys in store, a coupon can be offered as a motivating force to buy on the web.</p>

<p><em>All the data are aggregated from Google Trends On July 16 2015</em></p>

		]]></description>
	  </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
