<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
   
    <title>RealJenius.com - Category: Loyalty Trends</title>
   
   <link>http://realjenius.com</link>
   <description>I'm a software developer in the game industry, and have been (for better or worse) coding on the Java platform for the last decade. I also do all my own stunts.</description>
   <language>en-us</language>
   <managingEditor>R.J. Lorimer</managingEditor>
   <atom:link href="rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

    
	  <item>
        <title>Top 5 Customer Loyalty Trends of 2016</title>
        <link>http://realjenius.com/blog/top-5-customer-loyalty-trends-2016</link>
		<author>R.J. Lorimer</author>
		<pubDate>2016-01-02T00:00:00+05:30</pubDate>
		<guid>http://realjenius.com/blog/top-5-customer-loyalty-trends-2016</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[
		   <p>In all actuality client experience does make a difference. Brands that can give fun, satisfying encounters through great deals stages and additional items like dedication projects have the capacity to catch more rehash clients, who pivot and get new clients they could call their own through image evangelism.</p>

<ul>
  <li>Omni-channel Engagement</li>
  <li>Enthusiastic LOYALTY</li>
  <li>Client examination takes focal point of the audience.</li>
  <li>Personalization and accomplice showcasing</li>
  <li>Experiential prizes = greatest effect.</li>
</ul>

<p class="ui image fluid lazy"><img src="https://pegke.com/public/img/top-5-customer-loyalty-trends-of-2016.jpg" alt="Customer Loyalty Trends Of 2016" /></p>

<h2 id="1-omni-channel-engagement">1. Omni-channel Engagement</h2>
<p>Customer Loyalty Program venturing past the normal deals limits is one sign that marking has turn out to be more about thoughts than items. Clients have day in and day out access to the brands they cherish through online networking and cell phones. Brands, thusly, have new venues to achieve their center business without needing to envision pedestrian activity or exposures to outbound showcasing promotions.</p>

<p>Drawing in clients through substance or balanced cooperations makes a relationship that does not end at the checkout line. Brands that have the capacity to outfit the force of these numerous levels of correspondence to convey a firm, including brand message will be more inclined to succeed in an inexorably advanced environment.</p>

<h2 id="2-enthusiastic-loyalty">2. Enthusiastic LOYALTY</h2>
<p>Reliability projects are customarily considered as a rationale based quality suggestion. “Take an interest through these buys and get more esteem consequently,” are the directions conveyed to clients.</p>

<p>Nonetheless, this simply right-cerebrum driven support is now and again insufficient. Client dedication can be all the more adequately earned through enthusiastic, left-cerebrum thinking also.</p>

<h2 id="3-client-examination-takes-focal-point-of-the-audience">3. Client examination takes focal point of the audience.</h2>
<p>Measuring dedication has never been simple. For quite a long time, we’ve moved around various imperative KPIs. Details like LTV, RFM, recency of visit, number of prizes recovered, number of individuals in your reliability system, and others have helped us gage regardless of whether our endeavors in un-averingness are working.</p>

<h2 id="4-personalization-and-accomplice-showcasing">4. Personalization and accomplice showcasing</h2>
<p>We are bullish on this one. BigDoor is really fixated on partner showcasing, as we trust its vital to truly knowing how well your un-averingness endeavors are performing. Indeed, we keep a control client gather in every customer execution of our dedication program for this accurate reason — to demonstrate the amount of quality our innovation.</p>

<h2 id="5-experiential-prizes--greatest-effect">5. Experiential prizes = greatest effect.</h2>
<p>Prizes matter. We all know this. The previous couple of years we’ve seen the greatest brands on the planet re-put into their clients and genuinely welcome them in an assortment of ways. We think 2015 will get a shift how clients are remunerated for dedication. As opposed to just give out rebates or your most recent organization swag, we think brands will conceptualize energizing, novel, experiential prizes for their most connected with clients.</p>

		]]></description>
	  </item>
    
	  <item>
        <title>6 Customer Loyalty trends around the World</title>
        <link>http://realjenius.com/blog/customer-loyalty-whats-happening-around-world</link>
		<author>R.J. Lorimer</author>
		<pubDate>2015-11-10T00:00:00+05:30</pubDate>
		<guid>http://realjenius.com/blog/customer-loyalty-whats-happening-around-world</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[
		   <p>Reward programs are intended to exactly deliver this – be able to track and reward customer behavior. Statistics also indicate that consumer participation in rewards programs is on the rise across all demographic segments. With more customers choosing to do coupon and bargain shopping in the store, the reward programs that provide personalized rewards will prove to be differentiators if implemented with a laser sharp focus on targeted customer segments.</p>

<p>Best-Practices to take customer loyalty program to the next level.</p>

<ul>
  <li>Segment Based Personalization</li>
  <li>“Value”Driven</li>
  <li>“Personalize” Rewards</li>
  <li>Reward “In-store”</li>
  <li>Cross-Channel “Common” Messaging</li>
  <li>Break Boundaries for acquiring Customers</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="1-segment-based-personalization">1. Segment Based Personalization</h3>

<p>The way to winning the devotion diversion is to have the capacity to rightly fragment clients, and make offers in light of the sections’ profiles. Retailers are doing this in numerous ways – selecting clients in distinctive levels with clients getting the opportunity to sign-up on less premium levels and retailers having control on moving up to the high premium levels (with better advantages). The division is ordinarily based on present/saw ROI and/or the client’s propensity.</p>

<h3 id="2-valuedriven">2. “Value”Driven</h3>

<p>Today’s customer loyalty program can’t stand to remain a ‘rebate card’ and need to broaden past plain rewards. Retailers are moving from focuses and rebates to customized administrations, exchanging prizes to philanthropy projects, green activities, night-time shopping, access to item manuals, formulas, articles, “how to”guides and bulletins.</p>

<h3 id="3-personalize-rewards">3. “Personalize” Rewards</h3>

<p>Certain retailers make “clubs”that mirror clients’ enthusiasm for particular classes and permit the clients to infer unmistakable and elusive advantages by being individuals from these clubs. Some cases of clubs advanced by retailers are “Child Clubs”,”Home Décor Clubs”, “Natural Foods Club” and so on . This is another path for the clients to inform retailers concerning their extraordinary enthusiasm for certain classes</p>

<h3 id="4-reward-in-store">4. Reward “In-store”</h3>

<p>Moment satisfaction at the Point of Sale or In-store as far as offers on items, moment coupons for next buy, occasion based dialogs/messages (e.g. extraordinary occasions like birthdays or dropping a thing in the internet shopping basket), thankfulness for a high total assets client are a percentage of the opportunity zones for retailers.</p>

<p>Retailers gather data about clients and their shopping propensities and utilization it to manufacture an exact picture of customer interest, plan exact advancements in light of information investigation and convey it in-store. POS is advancing as a complex instrument equipped for managing this gigantic measure of client and business insight.</p>

<h3 id="5-cross-channel-common-messaging">5. Cross-Channel “Common” Messaging</h3>

<p>Huge retailers working various organizations and connecting at numerous client touch-focuses are concentrating on incorporating the faithfulness project to guarantee that the client has admittance to the same offerings over the channels.</p>

<h3 id="6-break-boundaries-for-acquiring-customers">6. Break Boundaries for acquiring Customers</h3>

<p>Retailers are additionally utilizing faithfulness projects to spur multi-channel connection, for instance if a purchaser normally buys in store, a coupon can be offered as a motivating force to buy on the web.Huge retailers working various organizations and connecting at numerous client touch-focuses are concentrating on incorporating the faithfulness project to guarantee that the client has admittance to the same offerings over the channels.</p>

<p>Retailers are additionally utilizing faithfulness projects to spur multi-channel connection, for instance if a purchaser normally buys in store, a coupon can be offered as a motivating force to buy on the web.</p>

<p><em>All the data are aggregated from Google Trends On July 16 2015</em></p>

		]]></description>
	  </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
